How to shine, I was the fire beneath their skin
I am the whisper in the dark you fear
And the truth you wake to let begin
I am the mirror, no lie survives
break them into truth
Echoes through the night
That's how you know the haunts alive
Lights flicker chats in a riot
And someone goes about to die
Heroes in loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks cracking jokes keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling the troll start crying ghost just glens. Let's fucking go
And now we're flying
May I have permission to crash out Ghost already did, he took the whole crowd
Hard to go, voice of fire Wingo shows up, the stakes get higher
Dum dum, that's his war cry sound Every hater, the gets spun right round
When the chat goes cold, he brings it loud His ghost of a baby psych, he's proud
Baby, Psyche's Proud
Why's he still around, but kindness is rare on this battleground
He saw my fall, still chose to believe
When most just laughed and chose to leave
He's the king of the late night ring
Creshing out with the heart that sings
Generous soul, half-sane, half-storm
Breaking arms just by staying warm
I have permission to crash out
You already know Ghost Runs this town
It goes through the stream
Let's fucking go
Become the dream
Dum dum to the ones who doubt
He's the reason the flame never went out
So raise your glass the ghosts are out
It's Ghost over forever loud
Permission to crash out
Yes, you may
We already know
By the way
Hey
Sorry, I crashed out. I almost crashed out there for a minute. I like the old song better and I still have it
You sent it to me. Can I send it back to you?
I can put the like the one that goes already did the other one that goes the same lyrics
That's the same lyrics and everything. It's just
I can get that song too. I just thought I'd make it
I like you think but personally me personally, I like the older song though. Um, I'm just old school, I guess, you know
So let me see. Um, I can like
I'm looking you know now we oh now we have another guest. Hold on a second
Hi, oh shit another one. Oh god, what up signal? Oh
Another one
My signal god requests next time we talk. Can you put a beanie on and I love your beanie by the way
Can you put red and white stripes on?
It'd be like where's water?
We're a signal we don't know we'll find them
Can you stop doing that? You're freaking me out, dude. It's like that's my own movie. Don't do that
What's he doing now again, I don't know why are you up here for so you know, you're gonna break to ask
Are you here to hang out? Why do you let me ask you a question?
Why do you fucking exist?
Hey, why is your mic so loud?
Um, I mean, that's a good question, brother.
I think we can get into it.
Why do I'm not asking like why do why do we exist?
Why do humans exist?
I'm asking why do you exist?
What's my purpose here?
Why do you exist?
So I think that was a question I'm asking.
What's my purpose?
Like my personal this channel. Well, I fucking I love me bait and I crush all these fucking retards like you
I crush you as well. Um, I think that's my purpose. Would you like to get in depth with it? I don't I don't think I don't understand the question
Yeah, kind of rude lead well signal, I don't know why the fuck you'd lay him back up there after all the shit
He's done to us. Well, if you say the word this dude this dude is literally porn bomb before
A mini, not once, not twice, but many, many, many times.
Yo, are you done crying?
Where the fuck are you going back up here?
What's up my channel?
Ghost, you're pathetic.
It's not my channel.
You are pathetic.
It's not this channel.
Are you done crying?
Or what?
He didn't come on me. I think he put a beat I think
Motherfucker I'm talking about you. Yes. He did come on you many times. It was perfect. Yes. He did
He put up beat his boobs one time. That was like an accident. No, he didn't know he didn't think that's not all he did
Are you talking with that's not all he did
No signal is not all you did will you go ahead and admit it since like right now like what you did
Yeah, bro to last a hundred times literally
You broke and you yes some pictures what at least three times on sites what two times on sites, I think
I'm not talking about that. I know what the fuck I'm talking about don't question. I know what the fuck I'm talking about
He showed us it wasn't his thing, but he showed a dick just cuz not his
Oh, yeah, those are there's like
What do you think psyche psyche as much as as much as you want to call me and in selling all these things
People like ghosts are like careful careful careful. What are you about to do?
Careful. That's right. These people are just like a problem to society. Oh
They're like too retarded you can't really do anything with them
Yeah, I mean like it's like you know, we have you go to you go to prison because you do these things or you
I don't know the best case scenario for these kinds of people is they live a shallow life
where they like
Resent the shallowness of their life
Talk shit about people. I don't know what to talk about like that's like that's the crazy thing
People like this as much as they like talk and more of it is them convincing themselves. It's like they're miserable
and anybody that has the need to put down others to put themselves up as miserable and pathetic
and it's even more pathetic if you're a successful adult and you have your own family
you have a career you make a lot of money you have a wife that loves you right
and then and then you join the stream and you want to talk shit about people
Well, that's just like that's just all the more pathetic if you're a if you're a math head, right?
And this is what you do you got on that money? Okay, fine
You're like doing will off you make good money you have a career you have a family of kids
Would you like me and this is what you do on your fun? You want to like?
What is that is that this is like the sort of thing where it's like is this saying more about me or is this saying more about you?
Sort of deal, you know what I mean?
I take a piss shut up to you ghost. I'm gonna go your name
Fuck you dumb dumb I
Don't like this dude so I can you know that you let him back up here. You know, I didn't like this dude
But that's cool. It's your panel. I'm glad that you don't like me. You're a faggot
Enjoy your piss, bro
This dude has showed for bomb you at least three times. He's also broke TOS. I can tell I don't even know the number
Hey, so I can did we not
Middle school
teacher you didn't see you turn your back teacher you didn't see what he did
fucking retarded dude shut the fuck up dude you're literally like a bitch you're
literally like you're the kid that didn't get your ass beat hard enough like
that's why you're a bitch you're literally bitching like this because you
ain't get your ass beat enough
Shout out to you. You went to a good safe. You you went you grew up in a good and safe
When you didn't get your ass be a verbally I'm sorry you didn't get your ass beat enough
You're fucking retarded dude. Shout out to you. Well, I have a question. Shout out to you my boy. Would you like to hope it sir?
You have your pants now verbally do it. I would I would like what I was like
Thank you for your request what I would like for you is to turn your camera
And speak the words that you're saying with the face
Associated with the voice
That's the sort of idea. That's the sort of time that I'm on. You know what I mean?
I literally just want more or less why it's at the center and shut the fuck up like you should do
I'm sorry, this dude actually like
Quiet and sit there with your camera off. You're gonna let him back up. Sit there with your camera
I'm trying to look out for my brother. Not showing your face feeling comfortable thinking that nobody knows what you look like
So you have a free liberty. Everybody knows what I look like and that's be as you want to be
Instead of as you should be
Everybody knows what I look like. What's what's your what's your argument? Go ahead
You don't have one because you're retarded. Okay, so I just did literally made you in your panel before literally at least three times
I remember because he's fucking so degenerate. What would you let him back up here?
Question a dissu-question. It's your panel not my family
Yeah, but you you said that shit last time when he was up here and then he did some shit and then you ended the whole panel for everyone
I know, but that's not fun for anyone. That's not fun for us. I've never I've never
Down
I'll say this. I've said this many times and I'll say it again
Hey, I have never taken second panel down retard. Hey, other people have done things
They're my name. You didn't say the same thing. Never do that. You're not that powerful. It's just that simple. There's there's people that are
You fucking you don't know you don't understand what I'm saying to you as as
Pathetic as one might imagine
You know like these people they
I'm not gonna say work a whole week and then on their weekend. This is what they do for their free time like the
Drama and they're like
Manufacturing drama right fine. You want to join streams and talk shit. Okay?
I'll give you but these people they join these streams
Factured drama
Normally, I would have no problem with that right you want to manufacture drama
At least have the balls to like show your face behind it
It's not it's not it doesn't seem like an unreasonable thing to say okay. Well if you're gonna be doing all of this shit
Put your balls behind what you're saying, you know, I mean, but but people want to have it both ways
They want to be hiding their camera and then they also want to be
Talking their shit I
Understand you can have it both ways, but you're just a bitch
Why you have to go tonight
He's a good guy. He actually what psyche I go after anybody that's that's like going after me man
You know the deal man, right? This goes without these sort of things it goes without saying he said he pornbombed itself
And you kind of maybe you know
Nope, I've never porn bombed you and I've never done anything that hurt your channel. Absolutely not
I've said this I've said this many times and I'll say this again
If I wanted to take someone's channel down, if I wanted to hurt someone's YouTube channel,
I want to say right now, that if that was my goal, I could...
Yo, what's up?
Um, ghost, thank you. He, um, he paid for sick to be kicked off for the night.
Hey, what's up? How you doing?
Yeah, I'm pretty good. What's up? I like your red lighting.
You look like you're in a, a whorehouse. I'm just kidding.
Thank you.
Oh, red light district or something. I've been to Amsterdam and uh,
they have a red light district there. Have you ever heard, heard of that?
Yeah, I've heard of it. I probably experienced not in Amsterdam, but
it was a, uh, they have like all these just windows.
And there's some of the women are pretty
What about the oh, what are you talking about, bro? Oh
Jack hey be careful brother. Hey be careful. I had uh, I had
Check in as wet. Oh fuck. Oh my god. That's heartburn. I guarantee
I usually drink fireball, but I had a patient.
My first patient had to die from me today.
Yeah, my first patient ever died on me today, so.
Oh, sorry.
Oh my gosh, was I thinking, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, it was rough.
I had a really rough day today.
Well, I think you deserve a drink.
I think you deserve a toast.
I mean, I would drink, not a toast,
could bring a toast to you.
Dude, I've been a nurse now almost two years.
This is the first patient under my care that died, like.
Mm-hmm. I apologize man. I'm sorry that happened to you
I'll take a shot with you if you want. I'll take a shot with you. Hell. Yeah, bro. Let's go. Yep
Countdown three two one will go. Um, I'm ready. You count it down
Yep, okay, that's that's fair. All right three two one
Damn that burn. Oh, I'm not used to that. I don't think that shit brother
No, drink that shit brother you used to I don't drink hard liquor
We had to give CPR to this patient for like 15 minutes until the EMS came
Well, let me let me let you know a little secrets. You guys want to be real about it. Um
When you guys I'm not gonna give you all they're gonna Google me and they already got my picture, but uh
Look, uh, but two years ago, uh, there was a kid that uh, autistic kids by the way
and uh, yeah, and we had a pond in our parks. I used to be the
Recreation coordinator for the parks
from my city. And uh, we have a pool right over there. We have like a river, but uh,
he went over there and I think he was just a dozen. He drowned and I was the first one
that found him. Yeah. And I was trying to go. Did you push him in the water? Did you when
You know, this is this is some serious shit. It's like give me like literally like it's like two minutes and then
Give me two minutes. Is that cool? Yeah, can I get two minutes? Okay?
That I mean that's there and I don't blame you but I didn't find him and
And I try to prompt him
It didn't work out and that's why I don't work for the city anymore because it fucked me all up
Yeah, it fucked me up tonight, dude. I haven't I never lost a patient while I've been working as a nurse under my care and
We got a patient. It was a new admission like 2 p.m. And then I came in to work at 3 p.m. And they were dead by 6 p.m
Like it was just it fucked me up, man. I was like
You know
Which is the horrible thing the horrible thing was like
He got the only thing that I have grown up. It's so horrible. I don't want to say it. It's gonna make me sound like a piece of shit, but
Yeah, I found him in the walk. Oh my god. So and then I bring
But I think he was already he was already done like he was done for yeah
That's not a good thing though
It was literally someone that came in they were a new admission like I didn't know anything about this guy
And literally within like three hours. He died like it was just just think of you
I'm like, you know, everyone would die. So it's like, you know, I'm I'm not a hospice nurse
It's like it's like I'll tell you a new detail and like
I know how these people did I give you a detail. Um, I didn't have a mask
So like obviously when you are drowned you throw up and I breathe all that shit and when I was breathing into him
I literally
There's fucking horrible, dude
Dude, I'm a mess from tonight, dude. I fucking we put the backboard under him. I was giving him chest
But now that I think about it, I'm fucking portal right now
Uh, but at the moment I was what that fucking I want I've never I want him to live
I've never I've never had a patient code under my care. Like that was very uh, you know
New to me, and I've been a nurse now for almost two years. I've never had a patient code under me
I'm sorry, I just worked there. I wasn't I was a park employee
Bro, I got I got pissed bro
I got there were these like fucking Somali fucking aides that we have work for us and they were like
Trying to like look at people like they were coming into the room and like oh we want to see a dead body
And I was like bro unless you're gonna do fucking chest compressions like get the fuck away from me like I
Got very mad but um
The dude the guy was
Get over that don't skip over that that was a good thing
They were like oh you have a new admission
Okay, great. I got new admission and then like within three hours. He was fucking dead
And I was like wow, this is new for me like I never fucking dealt with someone coding under my care like
Well, you know now it's like now it's happened and it's like you know
Yeah, a lot of the a lot of the guys that work
They were like oh, this is the first guy you ever had that coded on you and I'm like yeah under my care
They got me a bottle. They know that I drink fireballs. They got me a bottle of Jack Daniels fire. They're good stuff
Yeah, is it code red or code blue?
code blue a code blue
Code code red is a fire
Okay, code code gray is someone that like escaped like a dementia patient like they fucking escape
There's a bunch of different codes, but a code blue is I'm not it's literally like
And cardiac arrest like,
Well, you know, Christine is a nurse
and it's what's handy is that she has these henchmen
they're 90 years old.
And so she can actually like be a nurse for them.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, I work on a subacute units,
people coming out of surgery and like, you know,
rehab patients that they get better.
Like it's not like, well,
I used to work on a long-term
and pulmonary care for a year.
Christine said, talk to him.
I've had patients code, but they weren't on my shift.
They would code and die, but it was like,
not while I was at work, I would go into work the next day
and be like, oh, this patient died.
Like, you know, I never had a patient actually code
while I was like on shift, and this is the first one.
So this is a big deal for me, like, you know.
Well, are you gonna drink that whole bottle tonight?
No, I got work tomorrow, but.
I feel responsible in some way because I'm accountable for this person, you know, but
right
He was really admitted to my unit an hour before I came to work
Yeah
Maybe you're like a psychopomp, which is like somebody that like you know helps somebody into the other world, you know
You know what the crazy part is is like so I had to call the the the next of kin, which is the wife
And I called the wife and I said,
you know, your husband coded and he died.
And she was like, yeah, we were expecting this.
I never even worked with your patient before today.
Like I never even knew him like at all, period.
Like he literally just got admitted to the fucking facility.
And she was like, yeah, we expected this.
Like, I'm like, what do you mean?
He never sure left the hospital then.
Sometimes the family is is expecting it and sometimes it's been very difficult in the family
Do you know having to you know deal with the illness and it's like they know the light dude the I called
I called the wife who was the next of kin on the emergency contact list and like
Son and told the son
And like, neither of them even came to get the body.
They told me to just call funeral services.
They're not going to come pick up the body.
I mean, they can maybe see it.
Like, but it's like, you know, they're the people.
Well, that's, that's usually what happens is you call the next of kin and they come and see the body.
They were funeral services come and take the body away, but they weren't able to so funeral services came into the body away like
It was just it really fucking broke me like honestly
I'd ever been tried like that as a nurse before like where I had a patient die under my care and
Reminds me of that movie. The movie is called City of Angels. It has Meg Ryan and Nicholas Cage and she's like this doctor
No, I'm just saying the movie Meg Ryan's a doctor and like she's like
and then he did the patient dies and then the angels like see you don't know everything you're
not in control of everything it was nothing like what about what about
well let me ask let me get my one d1 and the other nurse on the unit
what about like what until until fucking yeah that's game what about the next like the nurse
Yeah, I'm sorry
I don't know everyone gets so quiet when I leave. I don't know what I was talking to you guys talking to me.
Bitch, answer your panel.
You told me to shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up.
Joe, are you drunk? Where are you?
Why are you being so abusive?
He's talking to you.
Shut your panel.
Why are you talking over him and me?
I'm not talking to anybody.
Okay.
Well, I just like letting everyone talk. We can't hear whenever I ask you a question. Who's you want to give us the answer?
That's not gonna play me like that
Don't play me like you do not play me like that you're
No, don't play me like that. I'll swap the fuck out you
Yeah, you ain't gonna slap the fuck out of me. I guarantee you
Well, he might be a faggot. We don't know. Yeah. Yeah, it's only a fucking bitch. He's gonna smack someone
I'll stop the fuck are you right now boy? It could you're a fucking bitch?
No, I'm a failure. You ain't gonna slap the fuck out of me. I'm gonna slap nothing boy. Yeah trust that shit
I've gripped that I'll open on me here
You're yeah, you want to you already won you won you want to run your ones?
God guarantee
You're gonna put on me
He's a fucking he's making
Smoke you bro, I will fucking smoke you
I guarantee
Go stop
That's one dumb dumb. Let's run one
This is what happens when people can't like fucking handle
Yes, that they're not fair retard. Let's run one
Okay, let's run one
Are you gonna sit there and suck my dick bitch
I think I'm done with them.
Are you guys here me?
You know they say code blue okay, but it went instead of what?
Well, they were they were like oh you shouldn't say
They didn't commit suicide
No one's talking your dick tie get the fuck out of here bro
Bro fucking
Street would suck your dick like
You want to run it with me
We're gonna sit down stuff up. Oh, you're so drunk
Mom big dog around here you guys are just taking a shot together and getting along and now you're fighting. I don't like it
It's like you're also gay. We don't care. I mean, oh wow
The fuck are you talking about?
Who cares if I was in bed with you?
You'd be like, oh, get out of here.
Why would I ever be in bed with you?
You made the claim to burn the proofs on you.
Oh, maybe like if we're like, you know, we're like camping or something.
Because you're gay and you're a faggot and you like to do gay sex.
But listen, but listen.
This is my brother.
I'm not having a bad life because you're too stupid to have your own back.
Don't give a fuck if all that is true. I love my brother. I mean so I think it's in the same bed a hundred percent
My brother
That's my brother
retard
No, I'm not trying to sleep
Fuck you then psych fuck you
Why are you trying to a person name on channel we know what the fuck you're talking about then go ahead
That's you when they go against people go ahead
These people don't even
It's like why are you so we try you know what the fuck's going on? It's like
Why are you so retired? You don't even know a male or female means why are you so retired? You don't know what?
Gender why are you so retired? You know enough fuck that I gave you I gave you you should have said yeah
You didn't do it didn't you?
Would you give me I didn't get it. Oh, I didn't take a woman out. I should have been I gave these out retard
Oh, give me the out. What is it now? What is it now? I'm on the team on dumb dumb. Okay. I'm sorry
Sorry, that's okay. Yeah, I didn't expect the fact I understand that
But anybody else here wants to answer that question? Yeah
No, we're all here dumb dumb
I need you fuck you Arthur
I need you. Look at this. Listen to this guy. He's going nuts. You got it. Yeah. Come on. Come by with ghosts for a second
I can't take it. He's so powerful. Fuck everyone. I'll take anybody you want. I'll take your best. I'll take everybody. Let's do it
Yeah, I hope he comes up
I'm gonna take some heat off of it. You know, right. He's not gonna come up then
But I just I just put the link so maybe he'll come
Well much of bitches around here. Sorry that you went through that. I'm sorry for your loss
I mean, it's not like you were more I get there said more sad than the family was but I
Haven't I haven't I haven't lost the patient in like a year and a half or two years like it's been a while
and
Yeah, I didn't even know this guy. He just got admitted like literally an hour before I fucking came into work
and he died within like two hours of me being at work,
and I blame the fucking hospital.
I blame the hospital for discharging him early.
Like they should have probably kept him for his CHF.
What is this?
Yeah bro, you should buy it, you should buy it, you should buy it.
Congestive hard failure.
I ain't nobody gonna happen to that, like me.
Yeah, you can buy a ladder on the ammonia and...
I don't know if something's going there.
Dumbass.
Dumbass bitch.
Really?
It goes, I can't hear LD, explain.
Hold on.
Plays a second.
He had CHF, which is congestive hard failure and...
He was admitted for bilateral pneumonia, which is he had pneumonia in both of his lungs, you know, but um
It's like, you know what, you know, but I think heart failure is like the number one cause of death for everybody
I think that's like, you know, the number one thing that happens is the heart
Yeah, but dude, it was so sudden like I said, he got admitted
He got admitted at 2 p.m. And died by 6 p.m. He was there
He was literally in my facility for four hours and died like I I blame the hospital for fucking
discharging him
And putting him in my facility like he never should have been in my facility. He should have been in the hospital like he was like
You know if you get off their hands or something like that. I
Haven't I haven't had a patient die in like a year and a half two years and
It's just real brutal man. Like I fucking
I'm sorry. Well, yeah, that's I work and I work in subacute. It's people usually recovering from surgery and like
you know
Nurses that are like hospice nurses and then like they're like everybody's past. I'm not a hospice
I'm saying that that if you were a hospice nurse you this is the kind of thing you see every day probably so it's like you
Kind of have it easier as a nurse. I'm saying is like, you know, not having to yeah
Yeah, typically in my unit. That's not the stuff that we do people don't typically code on like my unit like
You know, they're they're
I'm devastated like honestly we had this fucking guy for four hours
And he died within four hours of being on my unit like
Did you administer anything to him or?
No, dude the only dude I like I got to work at 3 p.m. I
Checked his blood sugar because he is diabetic and his blood sugar was
133 which is kind of normal for a diabetic that's within normal range like I'd have to give him any insulin or anything
And by 6.30 he was dead like oh, I'm sorry
We had to give him we had to give him CPR for like 15 minutes until the EMS got there
Do you at mouth to mouth or do you do like some kind of like suction thing?
So no, I gave him me and one other nurse gave him chest compressions
while one of the other nurses from another unit gave him an amboo bag, which is
basically it's like mouth
Resuscitation, but they put a bag over their head and and squeeze the amboo bag into it into his, you know
But I had to give him chest compressions for like 15 minutes dude until EMS got there because he had he had no DNR
He had no do not resuscitate. He had do not do not intubate like he didn't have anything signed
So we had to resuscitate him for like 15 minutes and that's that's the hardest part is like dude
He was clearly dead like
The AED the automatic electronic defibrillator
The thing that goes clear, and you hear that fucking, you know, the shock, we had that attached to his chest, but it didn't sense any heartbeat or any pulse.
So it said, you know, continue fucking, you know, chest compressions, like you have to keep, you have to keep giving them chest compressions until the fucking EMS gets there to declare him dead.
Do the nurse practitioner was literally there me and the nurse practitioner were like fucking giving off like fucking
chest compressions for him
Like me and the fucking nurse practitioner were fucking
banging on you know
Yeah, he was he was dead. He was fucking dead
Ghost
It might be a bacon. So let me see the name. Oh, sorry, brother. Ask me.
Okay, sorry. There you go. Okay. Anyone else want to come up too? I got the
dead body the other day. That's what we're talking about. I'm sorry. We're talking about
You weren't listening ghost ghost which he's talking about. Oh, someone said look they found a dead body. I have shit to do. I'm sorry
Mason said you're not getting tired right now. It's like, you know, because I slept all day. So I'm awake tonight
Well, Mason join because you're not getting tired as well
Oh my god, I sound like that. That's true. I hate when I sound like
Let me see. I'm gonna say some words
What do you say to me what do you say to me are you talking to you like that boy?
I was just kidding, I was just kidding, what the hell were you going to say, are you going
to say poppy?
Yeah?
I'll say that next time.
Oh, here's my link. I'm gonna pin my link right now.
So, boy, there you go. Oh, shit.
That's why I bought the fucking...
Oh, dude, put his link in your chat as well.
Yeah, let's talk about spirituality. What do you think of the do you believe in like the afterlife because if you believe in the afterlife and like
Dude, I don't I don't want to come out there. I'm very I'm very negative. I'm very negative about that
No, we're a Christian brother. You don't answer that
I don't think there's an I don't think there's an afterlife personally, but I deal with dead people every day like
You don't believe in the afterlife, but do you believe in like, are you a nihilist or are you like, uh, you know, an existentialist?
I'm an atheist, I'm an atheist.
So you believe in something, but you believe that there's no god, is that you, Aaron?
No, I don't believe there's an afterlife, but I think once you die, you become worm food.
okay well what do you think i mean it's like worm food oh yeah the body obviously does but
do you think we are our body do you have you heard like that we like even our thoughts i think i
think you just become worm food when you die like yeah but that's so you think we're just the body
you just you identify yourself with your body or nothing else yeah once once the body dies
you're you're done i don't think there's any kind of a spirit afterlife or anything like uh
I work in the medical field like I don't think there's a fucking afterlife like a person
who does work at the medical field they believe reincarnation there's a lot of Filipino nurses
I don't know if you noticed but yeah and so and actually my dad's nurses when he was
you know his hospice nurses were all Filipinas and like
I work with a lot of Filipinos, the nurse practitioner who took over chest compressions
for me tonight was the Filipino, like I have no problem with Filipinos.
It's just that I don't I don't think there's an afterlife when you die
I think someone in the chat just was asking like she wanted because it's like
Uh, you're talking kind of scientific and it's kind of like we are
I think it's spiritual. Do you have no sense of spirituality or anything or just you're an atheist?
Atheist has a belief. They believe there's no god, right? That's a belief
Believe that there is a god you can believe either one just as easily and if you're trying to hedge your bets
It's probably smarter to believe that there is
I think when people die man like there's no reincarnation. There's no uh, you don't know that for sure, right?
Obviously no one knows that for sure, but
Well, except people that have been
alive maybe or
people that remember I mean dude, I've had
I've had patients that have been fucking tricked and and in uh
fucking embittalized like
You can't you dude. There's no like
Okay, well, it's okay. Hey, what do you think Aaron? How are you doing today? Good to see you. I'm good. It's good to see you, too
Hi, LD. Hey Aaron
Yes
I'm a fucking mess
Are you what happened?
Maya, I had a patient die tonight. Oh
No
I'm so sorry to hear that.
I feel somewhat responsible because they're under my care.
What do you feel responsible about?
Are you?
No.
No, I don't think I'm responsible at all, but I still feel, it's still the fucking feeling
of like, hey, this person is under my care and they died under my care, you know.
No, I get it.
I understand.
I was just wondering like what your opinion on like you know, you know, or he's looking for some soothing or something
But he doesn't have any kind of like spiritual
Leaf, it's yeah, I'm not I'm not really just a more spiritual. Yeah
Yeah, it's
Dude, like I said, he literally got admitted to our fucking facility an hour before I came into
work
And then fucking when I came into work, they gave me report on this patient and he died three hours later like
It's just insane. Like I don't think you let the hospital. I think the hospital is at fault for fucking
What happened to ghost did I run him off? He's back. Hold on a second or who's oh, oh, this is another person
Hold on a second. I guess
Let me help you out with your little pity fucking bullshit kill trip
You let someone die tonight on your watch. So you suck
You might as well join them shit head drink that whole bottle of Tennessee whiskey, whatever you're drinking and join Alex
Can you be a bigger dick?
the
Think about the guy that's dead. You fucking retort. I had I don't go fuck about your little pity party
You're having this guy's having a pity party on your psyche channel, bro
He doesn't even give a fuck about the guy you're by tomorrow. I promise you he'll be fucking another hooker and getting drunk
Not giving a fuck. So shut up. We're your stupid pity bullshit
someone died if you're responsible shut up bro you're the devil you don't feel
responsible with shit and your little Tennessee whiskey is trying to get
sympathy out of us and it's not working homeboy it's not working my man not for
me anyway maybe these little losers will buy your bullshit okay hold up Alex
No, I don't know. No, I don't know. This is uh, this is Lola. I don't know if you've met Lola. This is my cat Lola.
Hi Lola.
Oh, that's Trix's mom?
Trix's mom, yeah.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah, I know. Alex, that was a little, you came in, you came in all hot, Alex. I mean, jeez, come on.
Can you feel bad?
Yeah, like we're trying to like, you know, we're trying to give at least some condolences
It's not easy like, you know, if your job is like saving lives and then it's like, you know, someone dies
It's like you might yeah
Fucking this like a circus act over here one's crying for sympathy the other one's scratching a cat Aaron who the fuck knows and
then
This is the circus act from hell
And it's yeah, who the fuck knows that's exactly right
No, Alexander, I need to talk to you. Please unmute
No
Alex wants to talk to you Alex go ahead. I'll unmute in ten minutes. I have to do something if you're still here ten minutes
We'll talk
Well, everybody's needed up
I get it, LD, that you feel responsible.
You're not taking anything away from the family.
You've got everybody.
No, dude, I had to call the family.
I had to call the family when he died,
but what I'm saying is I've never had,
I've never had a patient die under my care.
Okay, so extra part.
I was responsible for this patient.
So when he died and he was a new admission today, he was literally a new admission
I came into work and he was a new admission
And he died three hours of me coming into work like I
Just feel bad, you know, I've never I've never experienced that before
Okay. It's inevitable. I would feel bad too. Yeah, it's inevitable and especially in like if you know
you're a nurse and you're in a hospital that's going to happen. It looks like this family was prepared.
When three cops show up and they start asking you questions
Oh, so is there a question about it?
Like, there's something about what's going on.
Of course, if someone died, like, they're going to ask you questions.
They're going to ask you questions, like.
Yeah, but because people die at a nursing home,
a police game, you're saying?
That's crazy.
See?
Oh.
Go ahead.
Yeah, I don't really look at this as a pity party.
I think feeling responsible for somebody, especially when they just came in, is a whole different feeling, and I can't even imagine how guilty and responsible I would feel.
Honestly, the most relief that I felt was when I called the fucking next of kin, the wife, and I told her, I go, your husband coded and is dead.
And she said, yeah, we fucking expected that.
Like, it wasn't in my mind, okay.
Yeah, but why'd they let him out of the hospital
in the first place?
Exactly, why did they fucking discharge him
from the hospital and put him in my fucking
sub-acute unit, like?
Okay, I don't understand what I think.
One thing, what was he in the hospital for?
He was in the house. He was in my unit for bilateral
pneumonia
But he also he also he also suffered from CHF, which is congestive heart failure
Well, yeah, but if you've got pneumonia where I don't understand why they would send him anywhere
Is it like a hugely busy hospital that they needed the beds or something?
No, no, no, no, it wasn't like that like he didn't choke on his food. He fucking
You literally just had congestive heart failure and died like
Okay, so it was congestive heart failure that killed him. Yeah, it was CHF. Yeah, he had cardiac arrest like even when we had the
dude, we gave him CPR for like 15 minutes and
it was it was even the ad was like do do not shock him like
Would that have done any good actually I
Don't know. I've only seen medical shows, so I know absolutely nothing about anything and
You know and those medical shows they showed them doing CPR for like three seconds and they're done
Dude I had to give them CPR for 15 minutes. No, that's what I'm saying
Is it people you know when you watch a TV show we were literally giving him chest compressions for like 15 minutes until the EMS came
And they weren't allowed to shock him
Well, yeah, because the AED
Did not recommend a shock
Because his heart was already stopped
but I
See I gotta go take a piss. I'll be right back
Okay
Well, Psyche and Alex are muted. Ellie's going for a piss. I'm just up here.
Ghost, why did you take off as soon as I got up here?
Are you scared?
Thing that is, are you still here?
that was a black kitty for a minute. Oh, black kitty's on the camera. Now everybody's left left.
Fine. I hate y'all.
Manhattan South Task Force. Okay.
Big ghost
I'll tell you one thing ghost
You say the F word as in
That I'm gonna charge you a dollar
Every single time
You make lots of money, right?
You'll be fine
Let's run it ghost
The hell is that noise
What's up guys? How are you guys doing, man?
I'm here. I noticed that LD, I think he left the panels. I called up. How's it going?
Not bad. How's it going?
Good to talk to you.
I'm good. I'm good. It's been a long time.
That's it. Oh, and we have oh, we have another guest stuff coming up. We watch out watch out with the P bomb
You know what you know what it is?
Yeah, we got all the back
Fucking did you see me?
Yeah, I'm charging you down
The game don't charge me charges of the game
Arthur Arthur you're the same guy that hangs out with pedophiles, right and you're hanging out with me now
Yeah, I'm not hanging out there.
I'm hanging out with Syke, right?
You're my buddy.
We're hanging out right now.
Interesting.
So, hey, Syke, this guy didn't deny it, right?
So this guy's a pedophile.
I'm sad, though.
You're accusing me.
And you want me to be a pedophile?
No, this guy's a pedophile supporter, and he didn't deny it.
Whoa, he keeps saying the word.
Wow.
Interesting.
What's going on?
I'm not the one that exposed you, though, right, guy?
I'm a big, bad guy, but he's on panel with me right now.
Yeah, but I'm not the one that exposed you, right?
what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what are you talking about like what
I
Man show he's a cook
I know psyche. I'm gonna give him baby two minutes. Let him talk and then I'll talk
I already said I already said what I got to say
That's it. I don't know either one of you, but hi
Yeah, this Aaron's he had a Aaron is that ghost is it goes back ghost go see
Yeah, pay attention. He never denied it neither man. That's crazy
Ghost
Ghost you're on air. Please talk to us. Is he muted? He's muted. No, no
Oh, yeah
I just want everyone to know that's the type of person art there is and this is what we're doing
Yeah, let me let me let me let me talk to them fucking retards
Okay, that's another dollar
Dumbass pieces of shit down the fuck they're talking about.
Retard and faggot piece of shit.
Whoa!
You're on four.
I agree.
Let me talk to him.
And since Ghost agrees, he's on five.
We agree.
Yep.
I agree.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I know so I'm saying don't just don't say it please
Now ghost is up to eight and please keep saying it
Maggot PDFs like Arthur
Yeah, I said maggots maggots. Yeah, I guess. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh
You're gonna stop that you lost ma'am ma'am big on suck off
Big
Yeah, oh my god. Yo ghosts. Are you drunk today ghost big ghost big ghost?
Yeah, they're just in this pitch here
I'm
I want you to fuck off dumbass
what the fuck
what's going on
damn
I'm
playing
We have a question though, what did the leader do?
Intermission or what?
Intermission real quick.
Sounds like a quick question.
Okay.
10.
Why is it gotta be this?
Is there no TOS?
No.
I was born from a storm that forgot how to die
I laugh in the dark of flame in the sky
I walked out of lightning with truth in my hand
Whoa!
A storm with a spine
A God made of man
Eruge of pride, a crown of fire
A voice that breaks through every liar
A storm that sings and a storm that sees
Illigning mind that cuts with ease
We can call them by death
Fire does not hurt
Was ever true
Raymond, go!
Alan!
Mapirana!
Hey, how long is this?
Do this by yourself, but like there's a whole panel.
Jesus Christ.
There's a whole panel
Don't let me run my show Arthur if you don't want to be on the panel you can get off
I had to go for a second plus I wanted to diffuse the energy
So just let me decide how to do it and that's very rude to be talking over the song
And I was like play I think you both make valid points though. You both make
Thank you, Alex my show it's called my show
Relax no one screaming
Okay, it's over. It's over. Let's relax. Hey, Carter, there's only room enough for one homosexual.
All right, you want me to leave? You're here already. I mean, you want me to leave?
Yeah
No, I get
I get all the side I get his frustration like bro. There's a lot of people
And I get your side like you'll tell me how to run my shit
You want to run it babe?
Well don't ask me that.
Yeah, I don't fucking...
Yeah, I'll have to send you a brother
I'll have to send you to the other guy.
Get these backers out of here.
Hey!
You mean this is crazy? I'm saying the word.
You don't kick them out though.
That's crazy.
I'm just kidding.
I
You know
Yeah, you gotta kick Arthur I agree I never once said that I did I didn't say
Yeah, bottom right got to kick them
BG I think is up to five
BG if you just say it again, it's like I'll kick you up and you just pay 20 bucks. Yeah, just kick Arthur and we'll be good
I mean, I'm starting a swear jar for so now you're telling him what to do
Respect for Erin she had a question for me. I told her
When I get back we'll talk what's your question
Sorry, I'm not really sure that I had a question. I just wanted to talk to you about 40 hours
About the whole what?
LD you think and it's a pity party. Why would you think that? Oh?
You're not gonna get for your heart, okay
Because I was just you know after a while here. I'm say it over and over. I just going
I see what you mean. It was just said over and over and over again. Okay, I got you. I didn't come in for that part
People like you can't like four times
Nobody called it and I'm like, all right
No, I just wondered why he came in so hot
There's only enough pity for like my middle name is coming
Come on hot, what's your point dumbass?
I'm not going to give you any points to call me a dumbass.
I'm not even calling you a dumbass.
All right.
OK.
Any of them?
15.
Yeah, shut the fuck up.
You had this one.
Whoa!
What's up?
Kick Arthur.
Yeah?
He likes me.
I can tell. Let's pull my pigtails ghost. You'll be fine.
All I said was pull my pigtails and get it over with already whoa. I like that. Go on
You heard that Raymond. Why are you talking?
I'm sorry. What?
Sit there and shut the fuck up.
Okay, good girl.
Anybody else have a question?
Sit there. Good girl.
Yo, kick them. I'll take over from here.
So, you listen to pigtail pulling?
Pigtail pulling?
You know, I can throw a drive when you like a girl.
You just throw pigtails.
Exactly.
Boys and girls that hate each other like each other.
That's the question.
I can tell how much he hates me.
He's hitting me like he's hitting me because she's madly love you buddy. You don't have very many redeeming qualities I'm gonna say. That's the true thing that is, he is. He needs to get laid and he'll be okay.
Absolutely. Yeah, you know, let me hit. Oh, okay.
Just sit down and shut the fuck up then.
If you're not going to let me hit, then don't mess with me.
Shut the fuck up, bitch. Exactly.
What the fuck?
He wasn't a bitch.
No, he wasn't.
He wasn't a bitch or just a dumbass bitch.
Which one?
Oh, if you're not going to mess with me.
Shut the fuck up.
Just shut the fuck up.
Straight up.
You're absolutely pitiful, and you're up to 20 last not working
Then shut the fuck up
Like your heart attack man, come on coming down for a minute
Fuck up your
I
Everybody
Fuck up. Yeah. Oh, you want the whole panel? Okay? I got you. It's fucking all together buddy. Let's burn that
Never seen you like this. What's going on?
I got nothing to give like a
Plague yeah, me it's like then what
Somebody you hear something
Don't you have a horse that doesn't want you fucking retarded?
Yeah, you might never retarded.
Stop talking to us.
You heard?
Straight up.
Stop.
Yeah, you're retarded.
In the end, it's over.
I was like, to die for us.
So, what's going on with Alex, man?
I think we're the only ones with the cream.
Fuck when I retarded.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
With the glue that keeps this shit together where the pillars of the community exactly
Is that the real BG?
Because BG your avatar is not on it's a white circle
As a matter of fact, why are you even here? I want to see like it
Would you like to see what can happen real quick? Yeah one
Aaron you want to see him?
Gold or whose boss?
You're paying your panties are about to come over and get ready
That means no no no guys hello, he's gonna kick me
I
Was he gonna donate he's gonna donate like bye bye
Yeah, no, no here really yeah 100% dig yeah watch give it. I can even start the countdown five four three two one bye bye Alex
Yeah, so I'll be back though. Oh, I'll be back
The loser
But I do the same thing. I got a drop to when I donate
Boy guys get it in now. Tell me how much you love me quick hurry up. I love you. I hurry up
I'm out soon. I'm out soon. I don't know
I told you baby, I'll be back dick. That's 20 minutes
So you can ask you something
Can you oh, what's wrong with what's wrong with ghosts today? I've never seen them in this mood
I think he's just kind of drunk. It's like
He gets like a little bit. Oh he drinks. Oh, thank you
Thank you. Goose. Goose is having fun though. You know, let's
You know, I'm very upset. Goose come back up here
It goes make up for everything he did with those 20
He's gonna meet you. I think it's safe to say
I mean, it's like, you know, I mean, it is a monetized show and he is like one of the people that's, you know, helping, helping the, you know, of course, of course.
Sounds good. Oh, hey, baby.
Shout out to Ghost. Shout out to Ghost.
I see why you put up with him now. I get it now. I get it.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I'm not trying to defend them. It's almost saying it's like I'm not I'm not mad
You know, I don't get mad anyway, but it's like, you know, it does like just help a little bit
It's like because it's like, you know, people break him in break the rules anyway, and then they don't
Then don't don't don't it. Yeah, of course
You know anyway, how are you psyche? I'm actually really good today
Yeah, I got here we have um here comes ghost back one second. Let me just make sure it's a real ghost
Uh, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana, dana
What's your problem with not you psych, psych fuck off real quick, I'm gonna talk to them.
What's your guys' problem?
What's guys' problem?
Go ahead, what's your problem?
Hey, who's he talking to?
We were best friends like a stream ago now you're cursing at me. What the hell?
formation you're also fucking
autism
That's not a joke, bro. Come on, bro. That's not a joke. I don't give a fuck. Yeah, you're looking that's all the joke fuck off
Let me talk to this bitch if you don't mind.
What the hell is wrong with you dude?
We were literally best friends a stream ago.
I don't want to be your best friend.
We're not friends. I don't like you.
We're not friends. I don't like you at all.
Really?
Let me talk to this bitch.
I honestly thought we genuinely got along.
Play your drums.
Play your drums over there if you don't mind.
Let me talk to this bitch.
I thought genuinely we would get along, but all right.
Yeah, you might be upset, but we don't know.
You might be gay, we don't know.
You might like men, we don't know.
You might like women, we don't know.
But being the friend is gay?
We never know about anything.
Fuckin' retard, don't talk to me like that.
No, what's wrong with you, bro?
Why are you cursing at me, bro?
Gus, don't say those words like that.
Yeah, for real, there's TOS, bro.
What the heck?
I'll take it back.
can you apologize dude we're literally getting along like a stream ago I
would like to apologize absolutely nothing goes with the fuck he wants on
the double champ nobody can ever defeat me and I am the fucking off in the
I have a question for you. Yeah go ahead. Last time that we met on panel, you were very
nice to me. Why am I next now? What's your name? Can I ask? Aaron. Aaron Carter. Okay.
All right, go ahead. Yeah, the last time that we were here in Psyche's, you were very nice.
Yeah. And now I'm a bitch.
Didn't I call you a bit? Yes, you did
I
I'll take that back here, and I don't think you're okay. I
Appreciate it. Thank you
We were getting along like the stream ago, and then he's calling me everything over here leave
I don't know Mason Mason shut the fuck up. I'm talking Aaron
Aaron, I'll take that. I'll take it back. I'll take the bitch back
Yeah, I appreciate it now. How are you? I think that's fair
I'm doing pretty good. I'm looking for an argue. Wait now. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. You guys made up now
What what like what's what about you and me like what's going on dude?
What are you talking about brother dude like a stream ago you and I were getting
along we were like remember psyche right we were going getting along it might have
been a faggot man oh my god I got more money everybody
I didn't say
Ghosts I tell you to stop please stop saying it dude once you say that too many times you won't be able to donate anymore dummy
Purpose stop doing it
Are you Mason?
Bag it are you making oh my goodness tonight ghost? Thank you for coming on the show. Um, I you know
I have to you know, it's like I don't want to
I mean really I asked you to stop I screamed and then you said it again
You said it again, and so ghost it's I think it's it's that's not for tonight
You know, it's like he needs to learn how to cut off like that's crazy
Okay, so you're not Mason or drama, right?
But who are you talking to? Me? I'm Joe. I don't know who's Mason.
I know you're talking to me. I have no idea.
No, I thought somebody was calling you Mason.
Oh, no.
Oh, okay. I got you.
And how are you, Joe?
I'm good. I'm good. You can call me Joe Shippley. I'm good
I'm doing great having some breakfast I feel like
This has been a wild morning. This woke me up. I was so sleepy, but wow this woke me up
Sorry, go ahead where the Karen that is
Yeah, the Karen that is where is he no that's his name is not Karen. It's like I think it's like Rodney or something whoa
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to oh
Sorry
Alex is on a countdown
I'm not sure what it is. I don't know what it is. It looks like he's smiling in the chat.
Ghost you can me in the chat and stuff. It's like I can't have you keep asking
you not to say the word and you keep saying it and it's kind of like then it gets other people
to say it and they're like well he's allowed to say it like why can't I and then it's like well
because I said and so it's like if you're not gonna like go ahead and like
Like just like what I think maybe he owes me like 20 bucks for all those. I know I mean it's like jeez
And I think oh, yeah, I think that is if his name is Karen it would probably be spelled CA or Ry and he looks like the
Beautiful name
Thing that is are you coming up Karen that is Karen that is yeah
I could just see him, yeah. Saiki?
Yes.
When are you going to make a song for me?
You're like an Aaron song. Well, I can make you a song, certainly.
It's like, I usually will do it, like once I have like a few, like a little more of an inside joke with you or like a...
You know I'll do it for different reasons
But more background is needed more background. Yeah, it's like I think I then I'll put then it's like in your own song
Then it's like, you know, that's another thing like I mean, it's like I'm inspired, you know, it's like I'm really weird
Great things, but I do believe I'm writing songs now and that are like kind of universal with people and it's like
I think tonight people like I got a lot of likes and this one's on I did that is just very like
There's a shaman Aaron song. Oh, I can't figure it out. Oh, I'll be right back
I have a bunch of like, you know celebrating the year songs and stuff
Well, I'm pretty sure I'm the only tourist in this chat, but that could be wrong
Oh, there was something else that was going to ask.
So you're, oh, you're, you're a tourist?
You're a tourist?
Yeah, like, you know, tourists, like, I know a few tourists.
Like, Capricorn and tourists, they have butt heads
because they're, of course, they're both like, you know,
they both have horns and stuff like that.
Sure.
Right.
the um yeah okay so yeah we discussed about the burden and the bull and stuff like that with you right
yes burden and i'll read you about your birthday though if you haven't read your birthday particular
i'll read your birthday what's your birthday just say just your month and day i don't need for the year
April 28th okay okay let me see this is uh called secret language of birthdays um it's a really good
Book and they have a lot of this stuff on the web. No, that wasn't okay. So it says your your day is called the day of steadfastness
April people are capable of using their physical emotional or psychological
Presence in an imposing if not intimidating way
Among the most determined people of the whole year
They will not give up once they have embarked on a project or a course of action
against great odds seemingly contrary to their best interests and
That of those closest to them
they will hold out no matter how persuasive or commanding their opponents may be.
Their drive to manifest their position is powerful and what they stand for not easily forsaken.
Yet, because April 28th people are good negotiators and political in their daily lives,
they often give the impression of being reasonable, even tactable.
Though they appear accommodating, however, those who deal with them
eventually discovered that there is, in fact, only one possible compromise acceptable,
that which is desired by the April 28th person. Promises, then later reinterpreted,
bent, or even broken. The ability of April 28th people to wait is almost inexhaustible. In fact,
it is usually their opponents who wind up exhausted. This is true. Yes.
April 28th people attended their personal appearance and address
with great care.
They realize instinctively that a first impression
is often the most lasting one.
Consequently, they will avoid losing the opening gambit
of any life situation.
If mothers, they place their stamps squarely on the home, structuring the daily life of
family with respect to meals, hours, chores, and personal cleanliness.
If fathers, they will lay down the law and fully expect to be obeyed.
Life can be very difficult for everyone concerned if one or all the children are more changeable,
More highly evolved April 28 people make superb friends, lovers, and parents because of their
steadfastness in adversity and their utter dependability. They do well in positions of authority
because they stay in tune with the feelings of their subordinates. Instead of ailing through fear,
they guide and lead with vigorous, self-confident insight that's avoiding catastrophe. Less of
highly evolved April 28 people manifest negative results over and over again through their stubbornness
this horse is very stubborn, right? It's important for April 28th people to take themselves less
seriously. They must be aware of arousing antagonism in others by acting in a superior manner.
Fighting battles for the disadvantaged and downtrodden can prove far more rewarding.
Finally, those born in this day must learn to let go once their children, friends, or associates
To not always be in demand is important if April 28th people wanted to develop the philosophical
objectivity needed to occasionally rest and observe life's passing scene.
And so it says, the strengths, steadfast, dependable, solid,
this is weaknesses and flexible, domineering and sensitive.
and then it has some advice. It says, generally those born on April 28th are possessed by a robust
constitution but nonetheless may be vulnerable to heart problems, high blood pressure, or glandular
imbalances, particularly of the thyroid and adrenals. The whole trick for April 28th people is to
keep their energy flowing, avoiding both blockages and flare-ups of suppressed emotions. Over-eating
may be a real danger because of a love for a wide variety of foods. The eating of April 28th people
may be structured and disciplined to avoid major physical problems. The physicality should be
of sports of all kinds. Yeah, also with the venus, like, you know, venus loves fine foods,
they love luxurious things, they love durians and stuff like that. Very true. You know what,
it's always something with the throat, always. Well, I think, I mean, venus too is like, I mean,
it's like the throat too, and that's what there's a throat theme, like the throat chakra and stuff,
like, uh, yeah, um, there's a lot, I mean, it's very, let me look it up. There's um,
Let me look at what part of the Venus body Venus rules. Let me see
Venus rules and
Body part, I mean, I think the genitals, but let me see it says
That says the skin and reproductive organs skin. Okay. The connection is significant as Venus governs beauty love pleasure
aesthetics of the body and the reproductive system the skin is a vital part of the body that's health is closely linked to the
Planet Venus when Venus is in a favorable position. It promotes skin health and beauty
All those retrograde positions may lead to skin issues or concerns
Yeah, I must have had a problem with Venus when I was a teenager because I had like the worst acne, you know
And it's like, oh my god
Um, but I did clear up about I had some facials and it did clear up
I also didn't have a nose job and stuff like uh, and my braces lacy eye surgery
So I would look quite different probably if I had had some intervention
It's okay if we have nine view. Anyway, now we have 16 or third like look, I mean, it's like wow
It's like, you know, you never know how many viewers would get I'm not nearly as interesting. That's why okay ghost ghost
I'll let you back. Okay, but you know, you can't say it again. Okay. That was your last warning
You really pissed me off. I just told you not to say it. He falls asleep probably to hear I'm snoring yet
Ghost
I see his mic went on ghost go ahead
Are we are you talking like that ghost? I started about fuck you up. Don't talk to me like that
Drunkies. Oh my god goes. How much do you what did you drink?
It doesn't matter what I drink
Your point you sound careful. Okay, you sound plastered ghosts
Are you okay? You sound gay
I am gay let me accept that you are gay okay well i mean we can't accept that though
no we've established that it's okay you sound gay you sound like a dumbass you sound like you're
very tardy you sound like you're a dumb dumb you sound like you're a faggot you don't know what
the fuck you're talking about you sound like you don't know what the fuck like you really want to
keep going ghost he's gone don't play with me like it's like uh flop the fuck out you boy don't
Ghost I have a question
Yeah, go ahead
What is your horoscope? What is your sign?
Leo
Really interesting. Yeah, so you're the key cat
There was something I'm sorry
No, go ahead. I was just I was just curious. No, you asked me a question. I answered it
I said I did answer dumbass. I said Leo. Go ahead
Yes, I said the kitty cat. No, I really honestly do not know any leo. I can't hear you
You're a Leo. That's a kitty cat
No, Leo is not even a cat
It is
No, that's the that's the big thing. That's the line
Why you why can't a lion be a kitty cat?
I'm big cat. Yeah, I agree with that, but big big cat. Okay. All right. So we'll meet in the middle
How about a big kitty cat? Oh
No, go ahead. Whatever you want to go with your head
Good up faggot. Oh my
You're gonna owe me so much money
Sorry me soon
Go ahead and join us
No ghost, what's wrong with you, bro? Like honestly, like
Good join us in bed
Well, what's wrong? I said my bed
I'm just asking genuinely like are you okay? Cuz you weren't like this
I'm not bad. I said sorry.
But what's it? It's just, it's just, it's just.
Will you accept my apology? Will you accept my apology?
I'm just asking though. Was it like a character you were?
I said my bad. Can you accept my apology? I said my bad.
I said I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
I'll take it. I'll take it.
The big kitty cat
I guess this air lady your favorite number is 666 I guess no, it's 999
This is my angel number look it up. You're amazing
I don't have a main bone in my body fucking baggy. He's talking about 999
What the hell
I think he's like so drunk
It's like, he's like really like,
he's looking for a fight, I mean, really.
So it's like, he's just looking for a fight.
Hey, come on Lola, come on Lola, come on Lola.
Come on, come on.
I have two things on, let me see.
Ghost, take a breather.
I mean, it's like, jeez, I hope you do fall asleep
because you're just going out of control tonight.
I mean, it's like, it's okay for like a little bit,
but then it's like,
No, you don't have permission to crash out on like all the guests and be rude to Erin like Erin is just like nice
And it's like if she has a sense of humor or else like she might be offended because you don't even know her like that to be like
You know talking to her like that
No, it's okay
Yeah, I mean it's like thank you for being a good sport because it's like a lot of people
We would just leave the show because they can't take they would just be people as respected and stuff and as like I'm sorry that I like
Him to go like I need to control the show. It's like it's not the same funny. It's like, you know, it's like
I mean really I got so lucky to get my channel back and it's like he doesn't even care like about like I'm asking him to like follow
Terms of service, which he's always screaming about like arguing me like about why I'm letting people on for violated terms of service
And then he like he's doing it and it's like so
No, I understand that part and I don't get offended very easily. I don't worry about that. I don't like I don't like
I don't like it anyway, I think it's not good energy
to put out there, it's just like bringing all this shit
to my show, I understand, yeah, people can fight,
I like people to talk through things,
not just hate each other and shit,
but I don't even know, I think he's just trying
to show off or something like that, I don't know,
it's like,
Um, yeah, I think goes that's this the swear jar is like, you know, I'll let you back on the air for 20
It's done at $20. Um, okay. I got right here. Lola's having the like Rudy's outside, but like I was doing a cat some cream
She's like she loves that you're
Okay, that's love occasional
Oh
This is a this is cream creamer. Oh
Yeah
My neighbor had a cat named Lola to and also careless Kate those two
You know, you know, do you ever watch careless?
Kate the turtle I think they call her no
Well, yeah, she's pretty she's pretty cool
She she has a show to where she like covers the kind of the community. Oh look at the cat drink
Uh-oh, here comes Rudy, comes Rudy, he's inside.
Rudy.
Okay, yeah, you love screen too.
See, you have to have it for all of them.
Yeah, come on Rudy, your hand over there.
Okay, there's my camera.
This camera I got on T-Move for like three days.
I mean, I wish I could buy it.
I wish I would have bought like a nicer camera,
but it's, I mean, it's pretty good.
Capricorns are always like to save money.
You know, we're always about like saving.
Tell me, tell me about it, yep.
I get along really well with Capricorn's though.
You get along really well? Yeah.
I'm a pretty easygoing sign, or not an easygoing sign.
I'm a Capricorn Aquarius, like a mix of those,
which is like, Capricorn's very traditional,
and very like, oh, about the community,
but like the traditional way,
and then Aquarius is like the opposite, right?
And so it's kind of like, and plus my emotional side,
being gay, I think I have like more of a connection
with the feminine side, like three person,
I don't think I'm balanced or whatever, but.
Yeah, so the moon is significant for like emotions and stuff like that. So that's why I got like a lot of times
Oh, you'd love my new song then
You have a new song
Yeah, saline
Oh, okay, or saline
Saline I want to hear it
It's on my channel. Okay
I want to play you a song a new song too though. I have hold on
Okay, I'll play yours. I'll play yours after. Hold on. I'm not gonna kick him out. Okay. I'm just gonna have him in the backstage
So this is I don't know if you saw this is tonight. I put this out. This is like a new you just a new character unlocked
You can say that
new character unlocked. Yeah
That's so
Okay, so this is the here we go
Beneath their skin
I am the whisper in the dark you fear
And the truth you wake to let begin
I am the mirror, no lies survives
Come close below
Your scars unbreak them into truth, the new
The night goes down before me
The galaxy's kneeling gold
For the fire in my heartbeat
Is older than the world
Yeah, I love the Phoenix. I have the tattoo on the back of my neck says from the ashes. Oh
Yeah, I've been like, you know
I've been seeing the Phoenix a lot and stuff and it's been coming up like it's a common theme like recently
I've ever seen the in the the UN
Building they have this mural and it's like there's like the thing was made in the 70s
I'll see if I can bring up a picture of it because it's really amazing mural but it has a phoenix on it
but it's like he's taking off his skin instead of like he's like removing his skin I guess instead
of like burning in this painting what yeah it's like let me see um UN mural phoenix
Oh, you're so sweet, Joni. That's so nice of you to do for him. Thank you so much, Joni.
Like, the cats are all running around, but I really loved that. The creepy was like,
he was just going after it. Let me see. It was in the U.M. building. Let me see.
It's going to be behind them. Oh, yeah, here it is. Here it is. It's called the 10-year,
It goes come back up. I'll let you up. Okay, I mean come okay, so here it came same. Yeah, got it
Me see if we can see it kind of well, I'm not sure but we'll come up to boost too well
There we go, okay
Okay, we have a few people backstage too, so I'll bring the people backstage. Let me see who's that? Who is that? It's uh
I'm gonna put the banner up real quick
Okay, um
Let me see who's backstage
um
Oh, it's big big big and
The ghost link is pinned. Go ahead and say, is that your phone? I need to put the thing up. Okay. Yeah. Oh my gosh
Okay, so he's a rude guy in that
Oh
Okay
Oh, yeah
When yo, what's up, psyche are you drunk too?
Because here's the thing psyche there's something there's something called there's a disease called alcoholism
Alcoholism, what's that? I've never heard of it. It's called alcoholism. Yeah, that disease
Like autism. Yeah, but it's like a disease. Usually you can like, you know
Treat like and I guess alcohol is a disease. You probably just want to stop drinking as much
It's a disease you treat but never cure. That's the problem
Okay. Yeah, well
You can like stop drinking and think that we cured, right, right?
The problem is that diseases aren't cured
So you can't see slow down drinking you could slow down drinking right exactly, but it's not here
There's so many people that are that are that are just absent from alcohol and it's like they don't even care
Look psyche
Yeah, I
Mean open my drink yet. I have a drink right here. Hey Trisha. How are you probably for the best? I agree with them
Trisha join
All right, and let's let's hear inside. I'm sure you've got in say
Answer this concept of drinking because I honestly
Psychi I could say I could say that I have my opinions for their opinions. Okay, I
Mean opinions right now. I've been an alcoholic for a
couple of years so
It's not like I don't know what I'm saying, but like
Yeah
Disease and it just seems to me like diseases are something like you know
You can't like really do anything about like and it's like you know an alcohol you can like you know seek to help through
You know you can like you know, you know abstain and not all kinds of things like you know
There's ways if you feel like it's a problem, but you're kind of saying it's talking about it's a problem
Like you have this disease
You're right. Yeah, so yeah, I can ask you a question. Well, can I ask you a question?
Let's well, you know, are you can ask me it, but I can't promise you an answer
Okay, that's back. I just wondered how long have you been sober at one time?
What's my longest period of being sober okay, well
My second question that is which which drug or substance do you mean?
Just alcohol
Alcohol the longest I've been sober. I mean, I don't know. I like to try to be sober for a full day
Like I usually try to only drink at like in the late hours
I don't, I try, I try not, yeah I smoke weed, but I, and it's the same thing.
I try to only really smoke towards end of the day, and generally only once or twice.
Um, yeah, I don't know, it used to be a lot more, we'll say that much, it used to be a lot more than that, but uh,
Mm-hmm. I got it. Hi, Johnny Love.
Sure
Take me a shot. So, so now that I answered all those questions, are you going to get your titties out or what?
No, no, she would. Oh, they're already out. Yeah.
Oh, you should, oh, you should, oh, the song's your camera's not on. She can have.
No. She can have them, she can have them out. It's fine.
But actually, we had, we did have like Summer and Marcy and Spunky one time all got out.
They were all like, basically without their bras just covering their nipples with their, with their fingers.
and it was an interesting night on the show. I bet it was. It was, it was great.
It was great. Was it there for that or did you miss it? All these people came in the chat,
it was like a huge chat and they were like, oh my god, look at those boobs out. Everyone likes
boobs. Even gay people like boobs, you know, they're like universal. Except like, you know,
I wouldn't want to drink milk from 40 diamonds, but. I wouldn't want to compete, no.
I'm very impressed. I'm very impressed. Um, anyway, you know the floaty diamond is though. That's the kind of six ex-girlfriends.
I don't know. I'm going to say, uh, no, absolutely no. Yeah, you dated, you dated him? Absolutely no.
See her lactating on her only fans. Well, I have I'm so confused
Woman that came in the community and I fooled all the guys and like one of them was sick that she fooled and
You know, they all got really no I was not fooled by anyone
Oh, you have never I've never questioned my sexuality in my life
I was gonna say something, but I'm not I'm thankful. I'm thankful enough to have had limited
Instances of being charmed. So I get to see what people really are like
When you have when you have a bunch of instances of people trying to charm you
Then it kind of all
Blurs in
Seductress or something that has like charming. Well human beings they elicit your attention for reasons
All right, yeah again psyche. I don't know like psyche. Did you
Did you did you ever did you graduate college? Yeah
Did you ever study sociology? Yeah
How much of sociology did you study? I remember it was a not a very difficult class
But how much would you study? I don't know it's a I think I think I'm basically you know educated in the world more than
I was in college, but I
Mean if you if you take sociology 101, then it's not gonna be a difficult class
But what I mean to say is how far into sociology did you study?
I was basically, you know, I did other kind of classes.
I did like a bachelor's degree and then I did a marketing degree.
So, I was like...
You did a Crenshaw?
Not a Crenshaw. I did Harvard College a little bit.
But then I went to Brooks College.
You don't know Crenshaw?
Crenshaw, okay, okay, so I'm crunch on is the street like there's Hawthorne Crenshaw. I know there's a popular street, right?
Okay
Anyways, right as you know, I
Don't know I don't say these things that have Delaware
I, you know, I like to think that things happen for reason and they don't happen for reason, but
Thusly, I like to, I like to believe that things make sense and so
What can I say?
Things don't make sense until they do right right things make sense. So they do
Sometimes it's better to be direct rather than I try to make everything such a mystery like cuz it's like it's always better
Yeah, but it's like you but you but why don't you do it you always come in here like?
Talking I'm never being mysterious. I'm always being very direct, and I'm always being as straightforward as possible
This is an attribute that is not desirable and thusly. I am removed. I understand them
That's not gonna stop me from
Not being direct and straightforward. That's just who I am
This is my character
Wait hold on. Can we just do this real quick? Okay. Yeah, I'm gonna do that
Why am I still hearing this on I want to hear this horrible sound
dreams are refused to leave.
Is it me?
Ashes wrapped around my name, still lies.
Burn up, burn with flame.
They call me broken, call me done.
But they don't know the battle's won.
Underneath the darkest skies,
I found the wings I've kept inside.
The world may tear, may try to bend, but this is not how my story ends.
I rise, I rise, like a phoenix from the fall.
From the shadows I reclaim
Every scar, a silent song
Proof that I've been brave this long
They try to dim
How to survive, let the past burn down, let the silence break.
Watch me so f*****g.
You want a cooking stream?
Yo, I'm with you yo psyche psyche you stop kicking me out like a
Person I mean
Me listen Johnny we can we can listen to the song while we have sex, okay?
Can I show you something, Psyche, real quick?
What do you want to show?
I'm going to be like cooking something, you know what I mean?
You're doing a cooking stream?
I'm scared.
You're not cooking crack cocaine, are you?
Do you want me to do that?
I could do that.
I don't think you're allowed to show that on YouTube.
Please don't.
I mean, I respect that I'm saying I can if you would like me to show you the process I
Could do that
We have we have people like big ups, right?
You know what I'm saying like psyche you get it, right people like big ups
NYC smoke three three three
They're all like pathetic and they want to like put other people down
a notch, right? Because they can't be up as much as Psyche is, right?
A guy like NYC Smoke 333, you will never be as up as Psyche, because you're all fucking
dilusional, you know what I mean? Psyche knows, Psyche knows a guy, you know what I mean?
Okay, as much as I could say that you know, I mean he knows how to talk a shit in the right direction
You know, I mean
You're the type of dude. You don't get it. You know, I mean you don't get it
You don't get it
I'm not giving you a compliment and I'm not fucking kissing your ass and I'm not disrespecting you understand
It's not it's not like as I'm not kissing your ass. I'm not nothing, bro
This guy always wants to be a guest when he should be a host
Brodillusion
Yo, for those who know, they know, excuse me, I'm sorry, ma'am, let's hear it.
Take the incel on them.
Yeah, yes.
I was just going to ask if you were the one that wrote that song or Joni did.
No, no, no.
Joni recommended that.
So that was one she recommended.
Okay, alright.
It was great.
I enjoyed it.
I loved it.
Great.
And now can we do my song?
I'm really proud. I'm really proud of the lyrics. That's why I ask your um, what's your channel called I don't
He's 999. Okay. Okay. You're
Here's the thing here's the thing and why see
NYC smoke 999 you can join the stream and you can have a beer here with us
Okay, this isn't high school. You can't like you don't need to say oh
This guy is on the table. I don't want to be on the same table as this guy
You can you like excuse me. I'm sorry. Excuse me sake real quick
NYC smoke you can join the stream
You could join the stream dude. We're gonna nobody's like nobody's banning you from me here
Psyche is fucking cool, right? You let's people on yeah
So this oh so that
You know I mean
Psyche, I'm I mean now. I'm just trying to make a point. You know what I mean?
Okay, thank you. I mean, I don't want it to be interrupted, so that's why you're back.
In the darkness that has grown
The one who has no name
So hate and rage filled is this one
It strikes friend and foe the same
At one time it had less power
To do such harmful things
But I grew weak and it grew strong
Now look at what it brings
My strength is not to be found
Outside of me
It has always been within
I have been searching for something that never left
It was just buried too far in
I've lived in my head for far too long
There is nothing there but hate
I have so much to make up for and make right
I just hope it's not too late
When life is ended
All's said and done
you must realize there is only one
one set course one path to take
it was still your own to make or break
your path was written in the stars
it was known there would be stars
but at the end
the thought of done you realize there was only one
have you done anything that's made a difference in someone's life
has there been anything given other than heartache and strife
i've thought of the goddess and asked for some light things haven't been
clear i'm losing the fight it's getting too hard to think
of some good even when told i just pretend it's
should own can't change the past it's set in stone medusa's gaze has done its job making the
guilt inside just throb with every heartbeat every breath complete the stone or emotion death
when life has ended all said and done you must realize there is only one
one set course one
to take it was still your own to make or break your path was written in the stars it was
known there would be stars but at the end the battle done you realize there was only
I was born the two states of being in which I'm always torn.
I've tried only to show you the love and the light.
It became harder to do night after night.
I slowly broke down like an old carousel
and brought you all down to my personal hell.
It ended up happening, although I did fight.
My head kept saying, of course you can't do anything right.
I did think of three things I did that made the voice go away.
They happened in November and June and in May.
The things that are brightest are the children I made.
and the darkness to fade nothing and everything bangs in my head my only
thoughts cannot be said I once was her but now it seems I only see her in my
dreams it's far too late to change a thing I'll burn and rest I've cut the
string Wow
Aaron that's I know you did AI AI Aaron. What a great job wonderful. That was awesome. Oh, yeah. Thank you so much
I just did the lyric Shan camp did the video in the
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm good. How's it going? No, this is my first time here
I can't remember how I subscribed to this. Maybe I found it randomly. Maybe someone shared it. I did see LD earlier today
That's my friend. Oh, yeah, I saw him
Yeah, cuz I tuned in for like a hot second, but I was busy so I couldn't really like tune in for too long
I know this guy right here. He's always telling people he's my cousin to like get into places
No, I'm kidding with that. That was a joke, but I do like this guy
He always parties with me on my panel, but tries to at least but his mic is always way too loud and I fix it
I make him even with everyone. He thinks I'm making him too low
You know here and then he we do this audio battle and I just ban him, you know type stuff
Alex that was my song
Yo, I wanna see smoke. This is real me
Oh my god, it's you said you were talking shit about me. I'm here. What do you want?
This the real in YC. What do you want?
Big you got beef, bro
Yeah, I bet sick has us muted and he's tuned into something else that's how rude it is say can you hear say are you okay?
That's how rude he is. He just
Show I hate when he goes on his own show when he's on my show and then he's like like talking like this like on you
Hey, say are you there or no? You don't say anything within 10 seconds. I'm gonna kick you up the show
Eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
And shout out to NYC smoke nice to meet you. Yeah, who is going on man? You're my doppelganger. What's going on?
Oh, yeah big ups
Cheers
Your doppelganger is a chubby Filipino guy. Yo, it's going on psyche. Yo, man. I don't know how I'll subscribe to you
I know is I've been here a minute. I
Think somebody share your channel for my buddy LD
this guy's he was here so I listen for a quick second so yeah yeah it was going on these are
are you a streamer are you a streamer though you look like yeah I am a I am a streamer yeah I'd
stream a little bit yeah look at the channel I want to check out your channel you seem like a
kind of professional yeah i just chilling party okay this dude is hilarious though hell yeah bro i
really enjoyed it look good you're a new friend you're it's yourself you know yeah exactly i'm
like in the multiverse right now i've got fans out here you know the sky is trying to be like me
Don't know. Maybe I've seen him. I don't know. I don't know a Sandman at all
I do open panels basically every day like I drive around the city New York City and I do open panels from my phone while driving
Yeah, there's the same shit I do what the fuck
Yeah, I appreciate that yeah, you're welcome to you and uh, it's her name Aaron. No, is that just a picture?
Oh, yeah
Was that lady in the water with the alligator was that like a reptilian lady in the music video?
Let's see
I'm not talking about her I'm not saying if everyone was a reptilian but in the music video like I was telling me a reptilian
No, no, oh
In the music video. Yeah. Oh, I didn't know that. All right, my bad. I thought it was just like
Yeah, it was a dope video though like I saw elf
for like uh you know like something like that maybe yeah there's a lot of stuff yeah um
sham camp was the one that actually did the video i just did the words
but since i'm red haired she used a lot of red hair now i know like you know if you
create um yeah i contact creators like because um yeah great now i've got more dangers in the
I am you are okay. Do you have the ability or is your bush is your bush red, too?
I don't have one. We got burned off in a fire. Oh my goodness. Oh, yeah, let me see if I have any more. We have to get some tomorrow
One last thing isn't alexis 20 minutes up
um
I don't know when I come back up alex
He wants to come back up a little
All right, good shit y'all everyone y'all panel I do driving streams open panel anyone's welcome to join
You know I drive around in YC instant name and YC
And I'll see y'all later
Yeah, that's who funny does that guy come around a lot
Yeah, that is great. I have like a few like
pretty funny regulars. I mean, I'm pretty lucky.
Yeah, that guy is great
I'm really cute
I'm not bisexual
I'm a Puerto Rican
100% Puerto Rican
That's funny
It's funny. It's just true. I mean, I've seen a lot of Puerto Rican drag queens.
No, yeah, I'm not bisexual. I don't come from Puerto Rico.
I come from New York. You know, I don't know what goes on out there in the island.
You should do like those. You should do like workouts, you know?
I should work out. I don't work out.
What the fuck?
OK, you don't.
Alex wants to come up.
Come on, Alex.
That photo of you, Erin, is that you?
Like in that photo, just like a little edited.
You can see.
Yeah, it's just a little edited
Cool cool. He couldn't have fall asleep that quick click the link and fall asleep
Did you just bring him back is that yeah, wake up
Say he's sick. Oh my god signal damn he might be
Well, yeah, he was gonna teach you guys how to cook crack or something
It's not an appropriate time for that, but, yeah, Ghost is passed out too, yeah, Ghost,
like, you know, he's passed out, like, everyone just passes out on the show.
I don't understand.
Like, I'm not awake.
Oh, yeah.
But, yeah.
Yeah, I'm about ready to go.
Yeah, this is my only be like I have more in the fridge, but this is my bedtime actually I work from 6 p.m.. To 2 a.m.. So
I go to sleep around 7, but I'm not tired. I figured I'd drink one beer and try to get a little
I'm having a max harder strawberry pineapple. Cool. Cheers. I'm allergic to strawberries. Oh shit.
Well, I'll eat them for you. Okay. I appreciate it. Thank you.
But yeah, I just go live like every day down there, but not exactly every day
But um randomly I go live while driving open panel. Everybody's welcome party until watching
Okay, I don't what was your name?
NYC smoke
But they call me JR junior or smoky
They call you dickhead by any chance as well
Alex you're so loving what look at him. He looks like every other return in New York. You're
I'm doing young senior enough enough he put a reason to the same face. Well, you dumb little goatee
Thanks, Puerto Rican
We can suck by the way, I'm Colombian this guy's speaking and I'm the only one I can't hear him
Colombians don't like
Colombians don't like Puerto Ricans
I
Didn't like Puerto Ricans
Colombians of cool Puerto Ricans and Colombians hate each other
that's how it goes. Oh, I didn't know that. I had no idea that's how it goes.
Unless the poor ones got good money and the Colombians got good kilos,
then they become best friends, right? Then they do become best friends.
I'll become best friends with a fucking German asshole if you got the right shit.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. I'll fucking North Korean fuck anybody that's got to connect.
That's not the point here. Oh, yeah, no doubt. He's looking for a plug, people.
No, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I
Oh, man, like I do know I could get by but like, yeah
That's crazy, I can get by but I'm not the best. Were you born here?
Yeah, I was born here and I only been to Puerto Rico twice for vacation and never I beat you
I wasn't born here and I've been to Puerto Rico three times
Three times I've been there and I was born in Colombia, but I came here's a little tight a little you know little
Little young link nice, how I paint the Puerto Rico three times in my life
San Juan
El condado
I went to a San Juan. You had this trip
Stood at the Marriott twice. Would you say it?
When you say psyche
I was, oh yeah, are you in love with some guy named Eli from Puerto Rico?
Someone said, that's what I'd smash that in the chat.
He says, Alex seemed to love that Puerto Rican named Eli, is that true?
Do you know who that is?
What?
Puerto Rican named Eli?
Yeah, Eli's the one that got stabbed, right?
Or SC?
Yeah, he's not from Puerto Rico.
He's Dominican.
Oh, he's Dominican.
Who got stabbed?
What?
I'm Eli from People's Podcast.
He got stabbed.
Oh.
But who?
Who stabbed him?
Jonah, if you want to come say hi.
Jonah's in the Philippines.
She's really sweet.
I just saw, like, I've been a member of her channel, I think, for, like, 15 months or something
like that.
You can make up to $2,500 if it leads to an arrest and a conviction.
I do know.
I'm going to call.
It's on video.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, they raised it to $3,500 now.
New York's getting spiffy.
They raised it to $3,500 if you can help with any crime, solve any crime.
If you can help solve any crime, you got $3,500 in your pocket, baby.
Well, that's not gonna be a dark Alex. I'm not sure and you can remain anonymous like me. Yeah, my name is number four
If I filmed someone like J-Walkin, I could get like 3,500 bucks.
No.
No, a real crime dick, like murder.
Fucking J-Walkin.
What a real crime dick.
I filmed a woman J-Walkin holding my 4G.
J-Walkin doesn't count, god damn it.
It's gotta be a good one, baby.
No, it's gotta be a good one.
At least a felony.
At least a felony, bro.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, can I know can I film my own felony and still get the money?
Well, no, I don't think so because then it's like
What do you mean your own?
So you're gonna get a
Like come get me, but it's gonna cost you more in lawyer fees and jail time than the poor grand
It's not when you get out of jail. You have like four G's waiting for you. That makes sense
We're gonna wait 30 G's and lawyers
I'm gonna actually admit to it. I don't need a lawyer. Yeah, you have to
Stoppers what's your emergency? I want to report a crime. What is it? I?
I did a lot of felonies come get me
What the fuck?
So he's named you have my four thousand ready in two years when I get our rikers. Is that what you're telling me we're going?
Yes
Have you seen like it's a solid grand that's not even a purse
Then you get out of your business with that poor grand, you know
I don't even want to like that's too funny jail. I finally have a boyfriend like group showers. It's on every bus stop in New York
Salva crime cold crime stop
I didn't even think that was still a thing. I started thinking I'm like, who do I know who can I read out?
Man, all my friends are drug dealers. I can't do that. That's not really solving a crime. That's just right. I
Don't know. That's a snitch thing. No
Don't know any you know fuck. Yeah, I'll keep my eyes open now
But it's gonna take time to it's not right away. You gotta wait like ten years today convict a dick and throw him in jail
Oh like that. No, right? That's not right away
I need the money and nobody can catch me. No, it's gotta lead to an arrest. That's number one and a conviction
Which can take you
That's how the one case
Yeah, you're gonna form bomb that's how it be
But the story ain't quite what it seems
Viewers gather round out of kindness
Why is he doing this to us?
Yeah, what kind of nightmare from hell is this?
A performance fine-tuned to the core. Clicks and gifts keep rolling in steady, though she's
healthy as ever and more. But someday the mask may crumble. Truth cuts deeper than a trick.
He keeps on streamin', sellin' stories, layin' thick
Gymnic ain't really sick, just playin' that sympathy stick Spinnin' tails, go dramatic and slick
Oh, Gymnic ain't really sick, Gymnic ain't really sick Just playin' that sympathy stick Spinnin' tails, go dramatic and slick
baby
That's just Nick. That's my girl. That's my girl Kim Nick
Smash side it smash side it. I'm a guy. I know that pretend it's have st-stomach cancer to get paid
Yeah, seriously. Yeah, he told one chick that and then she got mad at him and then told everybody and then he had
He played it off like he had it and then supposedly got cured somebody donated like 4,000 to him for medication
He actually asked somebody on the side for like medication money
That's crazy. I need medication for my Moli
Right man. Yo, the funniest thing is he couldn't say the name of the treatment or the medication who who gets a
Medication put into them or takes a treatment that they don't even know what it's called
Something happened after Kobe bro, I'm telling you I don't know who's the vaccine or cool with
Something happened to the planet after that shit. It's not the same
Everyone's fucking crazy
The evil doer baby! The evil doer in the Yankee hat!
Because it goes on forever. Who makes these videos like I see IP2
It's a go right bro, say it was a wiggle
Say
Yes, the Georgie
Okay, we're there pretty cool. Yeah, he used to be moving
That's just scares me sometimes, but it looks like he's fucking I'm moving. Oh, he's fine
Yeah, everyone's pretty drunk tonight, I mean I
Smoke NYC. Do you see this thing with his stupid serpent or yeah?
I think I should bonk you on the head with it a lot of coat leaders have those I bet
Yeah, ask him to show you what's under the hood show him what's under the jacket's like
If you were huh, you want to pass the test my man? No, no
Show them the flag
Psychies the seventh inning my man
Can we all stand up for the American anthem?
He has to pass the test
He's got to see the plague
You got saved you got saved tonight my man. All right. Well, I have to do the initiation next time guys
Thank you for having me up
You're the best. You're the best, bro.
He heard American flag Speedos and ran for the hills. He knew. He's seen it already, I think.
I know. Everyone wants to see my Speedos. Everyone does. Okay.
Who's Speedos? Yeah. Okay.
Oh, you. Come on, Aaron. Come on.
Wait. Did you have Speedos on, Alex? No.
Thank you. Is there a clip of it? Like can we go back to an old video?
I think he has American flag speedles and his nuts fly out of him out of the side
No, no, he does flips in them, right just on the speed of not a fly out here and there
Out here and there yes
It's like a potato. It looks like a potato.
Just like a, you know, potato with like one hair on it. It's weird.
Well, don't get your channel taken down.
Yeah, shut up, Alex. Yeah, anyway.
Okay, yeah, there's a channel called Fish Chocos and Dick.
That's not my channel. It's imitating me.
But anyway.
I really do see him holding his staff, his cobra staff.
I do. I actually like that.
I like it too.
Magic of power.
Look at him!
He's in a staff.
He's cool.
That reminds me of the old man in your life.
They're great skill summons, dripped from every glowing screen
A ritual of dry performing
Not touch this bridge again
I know you do baby. I love you so much. That was me talking. I know you do Erin. I want to, I want to marry you Alex. Erin, Erin baby, we just met.
Slow it down. Slow it down or not. Let's bring it in. Do you think she's married? Is she? Yeah, she is.
hey what's up money for 20 hey skumma erin you're married
are you definitely uh oh yeah oh if he's probably sucking his dick right now that's what she's not
answering she's definitely married well erin thanks for being with me he's a lot of his brush in her
teeth but sorry wait what oh nothing nothing i was like he was like so
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
It goes and it's don't even know
Do not turn your head pilgrim
The air is thick with omens and hungry eyes
Keep your heart beat steady as a drum in the underhaul
No flinch, no tremor
For bread it is a door that tastes of panic
Chain reactions, coil like serpents around your ankles
I'd rather stand before the beast than crawl
remembers it's
was horrifying thank you oh yeah you know I'm related to the first clown we mean
psyche praise you we praise you from head to toe baby we absolutely okay
Oh my gosh, it was kind of this end-cales from movie,
but it was about like this really weird thing.
Like there's a school and all the kids in this one lady's
class all disappeared.
And so they like, you know, but then like,
there's no explanation for it.
Or they actually, they all walk out of their house
like at five in the morning and like disappear somewhere.
Oh, I saw that.
Yes.
My husband, there's two people in the house in it.
What's it called?
In hypothetical world, Aaron was married.
What would, what would he do?
What does your husband do for a living?
He wouldn't drive, would he?
Is anyway
You know, ah psyche dick he he ha he almost ruined our love, baby. He said you were
Married, oh my god
All right, Ronys, yo, hello
she's not married bro
Yo
Quick question for the three of you
You know when people play the victim mentality, but you get like victim fatigue for example like the BLM
And she's
Oh, you know what I mean, right?
I know what you mean, baby
You talk to psyche. I'll talk to Eric. We gotta let go
Is there any way we could divide the panel you too?
Psych you know what I mean, right?
Hey, no, he runs like you a Alex. God damn it
All right, Revando hit it. What's going on here? I'm interested in you guys know like
You guys know the whole be a lamb and like you get tired of it at one point
It's like you you get fatigue like BLM fatigue. You've heard of that
I'm fatigued by everything
All right, so wait, I'm done with you
With that being said
No, you're gonna sleep. You're gonna sleep for a month, baby. With that being said, I
Feel like I'm getting AI fatigue with psyche constantly doing
AI fatigue what a thing his songs are killing you
I love his videos. I like him too, bro. I like him too. Mundo. You can handle the AI songs
He's fatigued
Look what life has done, baby
We had tacos on the pier, wind in our hair
Half the town wondering who let this man out anywhere
July 4th, Lord the speedo was a war crime
But the sun saluted me anyway, said the fit was divine
Oh, what a year it's been
Friends became enemies, enemies turned back again
We laughed until sunrise, fought till it hurt
Sight further with every straight man on earth
Cops almost crashed and threw the chaos
That's where I heard fate whisper
You're right where you belong
Even if the universe gave you the wrong script this year
Inside jokes stacking taller than my trauma
We got chapters of nonsense
This is our own baby mama drama
I fell in love three times all before breakfast
And every man I harassed somehow
Still said yes to shirtless
Girlfriend soon, it's getting tragic out here
Even the tarot card sigh at you, no more ever clear
My liver filed the restraining order, D-high floating somewhere on the astral side of the border
And joker, man I had to crush the hit like fate
We rode off into sunset, like we're back on a budget date
Oh, I woulda hear it spin, brothers and weirdos in exit and a boyfriend
Roasted each other like family do some next damn near cry right there on YouTube buddy stream every fight every troll in my mentions
Well, I chaos dressed up as divine intervention through it all I heard the university. It's messy
It's magic, and you're exactly who you need it to be this year
Some friends stayed some ghost return
Some lessons hit harder than I felt I deserved
We lost some innocence, games, some perspective Turned heartbreak into memes, bro, that's it, flirt it
Flirted crash, burned laugh, got healed, got harmed And somehow kept coming back with the same stupid charm
I wanna hear it spin, spin, spin The wildest season of my life so far
And I do it all again
For the fans, for the friends, for the lovers
I almost had for the enemies
Who came back saying alright
Maybe you're not that bad
We live loud
We live messy
We live like a fever dream
And I wouldn't trade a second of this
Beautiful madhouse we
Call a team
And when I look at everything every tear
Every tear I just laugh and say
Damn
We survived to hear like you having posting panel fatigue I was like just
like trying to like did you say pussy panel fatigue or I'm hearing things she
said definitely hearing things okay no I heard something fatigue but I thought
No, because it happens my voice will do that to women that they just all come through the panel over and over in their
Pussy
It's a thing. I invented it
So I just was hoping you didn't some comfort
I like that one too that one was fun
Three times before breakfast
We're supposed to look for lab. It's mostly possible. The only time I didn't laugh harder than the time flirty diamond had that like
She did a somersault off the table and oh my god. I've got to meet this woman. Yeah, you have to meet her
I have a flirty diamond like I have my shorts, but yeah
She actually like you know, I ended up form bombing me a few times like what accidents. Oh, yeah, but
In any sense, well, now she's kind of like, okay, what, okay, hold on. Yeah
Yeah
Arthur
Arthur, okay, he's not here
Okay, I
Can't hear you come back and we're Dallas girl. It's just a spirit. Well, okay. Hi Amanda
Um hi Amanda. Oh, here he is
Okay, you know hello hello. Sorry about that. I'll read your wrench again
I was trying to do it, but I can't like it was like I didn't see your name
Thank you, brother. Yo real quick a weapon to say did he leave or did he even just ignoring sleep?
He was like pass out on the panel. I basically kicked around the studio because I don't
He was passed out
Now do you guys believe that alcoholism is a disease or do you think it's my choice?
I disagree that it's a disease, you know, I think it was a disease. Yeah
You think it's a disease
Or like I cannot like help it and like you know
There are people that it may be it is a disease for but I think for the main thing that it's like a very treatable thing
It's like kind of like self-inflicted rather than like
Like you just get it like how many right it's like and even they can say things about you know
Like a lot of stuff is self-inflicted, but we don't know necessarily. We just know that's definitely big the reason a lot of people die
self-inflicted weed smoker. Yeah
Yeah, I mean, but it's like weed is like not gonna weed is even better than alcoholic
You know, you can drive car and weed you can't really drive on alcohol people in danger and stuff
I mean, it's oh my god. You can so it's like you should have seen the first time that I drove after smoking weed
Oh, yeah, I went like
I got pulled I actually got pulled over when I was like driving home because I was going so slow and I was like 17
Yeah, so yeah, exactly. I mean, but I didn't get in trouble for weed though. Thank God, but
Well, we moved out in the country and my best friend lived like maybe, I'd say at most
two miles away and we got stoned at her house and then I had to drive home, yeah, about
three miles home.
That's what I was driving.
Thank God I was out in the country because there's no telling how many times I've been
pulled over.
Yeah, that makes me feel like they can be like deliverance cops, you know, and that's even scarier or something.
The deliverance cop? I've never seen that movie.
Well, it's like not deliverance, but it was a good movie.
They always have like the police department where the police are like actually like involved with the family and stuff.
Exactly, yep, yep, I remember.
They're a small town, they're all like related and stuff, so.
It's the small town, Dale, driving my car on high.
To have my car stoned to the gills. Yeah, I don't know if you
You guys do you guys are you aware that?
Alexander mayors, and I are gonna be hosting a Christmas special. Oh, I have no idea who that is. I don't know what I'm about
You don't know. Um, well, she's this woman. Oh, no, no, it's okay. You don't have to show us. I don't know who it is
It's okay. Oh the lady in your video today
uh this lady though uh the lady here on panel what's her name signal what's her name
Aaron Aaron Aaron she reminds me of stoner baby maybe she is stoner baby who knows
hey she she is right i knew it i knew it i knew it i'm not stoner baby yeah that's what they all
Well, Capricorns have a fishtail, so they can swim too, right?
What else do we got?
No, that's very true.
I have a...
Oh, here's, like, a gay pride.
It's Pride Month.
I love it.
That sounds gay.
It is gay.
That's what I did.
I know.
That was a joke.
That's horrifying
Actually farmers daughter
It's still a baby a real person. Is that what you're saying? Yeah. Yeah, that's you. Are you not her for often?
Hi, I'm for real not her. No. Oh, wow
Wow
You guys look alike
We do awesome. She has the she has right there. She also
Bush
I forgot I said that.
Yeah, that was the burning bush, everyone, worshiped.
Oh, Psyche, I thought you were going to play the other one.
I was trying.
You know one of my songs?
Something, hold on.
Oh, you have another song?
Yeah, the Selene.
Okay, I'll play the next one.
That's okay.
Thank you.
I just wanted to show you.
Well, I don't know if I can find it anymore.
Why do you look so mean in that?
I don't know. It's a what? Oh, yeah, here. I mean, you know, like honestly
I think a lot of this is spiritually channeled through the program or something. You're kidding me
And he's like, no, but when you look at the story, have you ever learned about the biography of Steve Jobs?
Tell me tell me
Like I think I know yeah, I know a little bit but he went through a huge spiritual awakening that led him to
focus more so on
creating technology to even the playing field between the rich and the poor
But he had a very strong base especially in like the Indian
Theology is and whatnot
One day, if you don't mind, maybe I can invite you.
Would you ever wanna do a commentary panel with me
about Steve Jobs?
Cause I'm a big Steve Jobs.
Yeah, which is weird, but if you ever want to like
Review his like like a YouTube video about his bio or something on a panel
I will do that with you because I would love I would love to commentary on that. I would love to
And so I figured out a way to get it to talk to me.
I would love to, let's do that.
He was like, honestly, I think a lot of this
is spiritually channeled through the program.
I'm like, you're kidding me.
And he's like, no.
But when you look at the story,
have you ever learned about the biography of Steve Jobs?
Hey, here's a picture of it.
Oh, he left, okay, there we go.
It's our Christmas special coming up.
It's gonna be the most epic.
Christmas special
Was it going to be on your channel on hers? Probably maybe both of ours
Okay, it's gonna be Alexandra mayors and psyche awakens TV. I'm holiday extravaganza
We're still figuring out the details of it, but it's like there we are. Oh, yeah, because I'm not subscribed to her
So, okay, so she's a few channels. Um, she's really good. I mean she's really um
Really a good watchdog on the community and stuff like that. She has a she has a Bible channel as well
You're just a Bible Bible stuff, but I'm no not Bible, but
Interesting. She's super interesting. Yeah, she's super. She's a very interesting. I've had a very interesting life and
Great friend of mine. She's been like a really really like
Just like it was a time when it was very difficult like for me
Like it was just like everyone's being pretty like terrible and like and she came in was like hey
You're doing awesome. You're doing good. Like and just was like so encouraging and oh, that's nice
I'm glad you had it in here is that was on her show
We talked about the Atlas and we talked about angels and stuff like that
Yeah, so
My name to small town. What is happening right now? I don't know. He's just a small town girl
I was at song that plays at the end of surprise. Hey, um, okay, so I'll play your song once again
Man, okay
I'll be on, but let me see, okay.
Oh, okay, so Erin, it's 666,
or what is it, Erin is what?
Nine, nine, nine.
Okay.
Okay, and is it the R-I-N-E-Y-E-S?
I don't know why it came up right away
when I searched on Google, but not on YouTube, hold on.
Okay, Google.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I'm just really proud of you.
E-R-I-N-E-Y-E-S, nine, nine, nine.
You gonna come up?
Is that how to spell, E-R-E-N-E-Y-E-S?
I might be spelling it wrong.
E-R-I-N, just like Aaron, yes.
E-R-I-N, E-Y-E-S?
No, just Y-E-S.
Oh, Aaron, yes, okay.
Okay, that's why, okay, got it.
Aaron, yes, nine, nine.
I mean, I just was playing it, so you can find my history, hold on, let's see, history, okay.
Do you keep your history on YouTube?
Yeah, because it's part of the recommended thing, or like, if you turn it off, then it stops recommending videos.
Oh, that's true.
song
Where is it? Oh, yeah here the battle. Okay. No the other one. It's LNA. I found it by the battle
I'm sure I'm sure up to you to subscribe. Okay. Is it Celine or Celine the Celine one? Yeah, the Celine one
Okay, gotcha. Okay. Thank you. I
Just mostly want feedback on if these are any good
You
Just before
Thank you so much.
So what is your process like on that?
There's no diddy part of your case.
Are you crazy?
What's your process like?
That sounds like you really put a lot into like writing this,
writing the songs and stuff.
And how do you decide like what kind of genre to put it with
or do you experiment a lot?
How many of you made?
There is.
totally about seven more on Shan's channel.
I was kind of a chicken to put them on my own channel,
but it's mostly goddesses and let's see,
there's one where somebody really fucked me over bad,
so I made a song about him and yeah,
mostly it's just really,
I've got to get it out of my head kind of thing.
And as soon as I do, I hand it to Shan and say,
okay, do what you want with it
and basically forget about it until she's done.
It sounds very, it's very, yeah, well, I relate to that a lot because it is like a catharsis for me too.
Exactly.
I'll be able to like, you know, I don't play instruments and stuff like that. I mean,
I try to play piano lessons that's not coordinated enough or like, you know, disciplined enough to
like get good at an instrument, but there is like a musical part of me that is like, now I'm able to express.
Especially with like the writing and then turning it into like a real song that was always like the the downside to writing is like
Oh, well, you'll never hear it to music and stuff like that. I don't know
But now I was like you can and it's like and then it turns into like something so
Not even just even songs that are just special to me like there's some of them are special to other people too
And it's like that's like so yeah, so amazing that we can like share things like that
I'm really happy with I think it's amazing
Yeah, yes, it's definitely an art form as far as I'm concerned. I know there's people that say, oh, no
AI music has taken over and I get it but in a way
It kind of helps me as I mean, that's all I can comment on is me, but it kind of helps me
let go
What's in my head?
Into something else something beautiful
Yeah channeling your
Whatever and it's like instead of just sitting with it like putting it somewhere
It's like the alchemy of like you know taking our even though sort of the worst experience of our life and like turning them
It can help other people that can inspire people that sounds you know beautiful to listen to and so
I will never put anyone down, no matter what their art form is, because it's like, I think
that AIs have basically been used, probably since the record industry started, there's
been forms of electronic magic, auto-tune anyone, now it's in our hands too, the public's
hands and so it's like people will be judgmental about it, but I think as time goes on we'll
Mixing themselves with the song like or like, you know, it's like it is an art form because some people are good at it
Some people aren't and it's just like, you know, right?
Just like I have some talents and I don't have
But I think one of my talents is able to like bring or at least I'll just say I generate them
I don't say I've played them or whatever. I mean, I write them. I write them
And I but I but I also
bring them into the world, right? And that they wouldn't be here in this particular one.
Yeah, I agree. And so it's not just like some random thing where it's just like I'm just having it
just like people think it's like, oh, they just it's just like just doing all the work and stuff
like that. No, it's like if you work with it, they can create it. There you go. That's it. You work with
it. Yeah, you don't let it do everything because it doesn't like
It doesn't have like a human sense, it doesn't like, it's not afraid of going to jail, it's not afraid of anything that we're afraid of.
to help, right? It's like, there's no kind of like poor thing telling you anything. And so it's
like, you're very dangerous in a way too. But you know, but it's also also we are in control
of programming. And so it's like, you can always work on these kinks, the programming and stuff.
If it's just saying bad things that was programmed to do them, obviously,
people take advantage of all these like loopholes in it. Like, the technologies are new and the
like give cars, not give cars, but they're getting so much money.
Yes, I'm going to give cars, please.
Just give me the numbers. It'll be fine. No, I think that's an unfair thing when they say that about AI music though
Oh, yeah, like we are getting rid of actual, you know people playing instruments or I love music period
Live music is kind of like more like, you know if live music at places people will appreciate it maybe more too
I don't know. It's like but it's like I think that almost the AI is so good that it's like almost in the cypher book like actual
Like you're so good like some people wouldn't even know and some of the songs I made I say I
Mean if I heard this song, I don't remember bias whatever
But if I had heard some of the songs I bring out like on the radio, I would love I would love them
You know, I was like, it's always yeah, I
It's good. I don't know. It's like I really am happy with the
the results
Well, see that's just it you've got people just hating on AI period, you know, they don't want to have anything to do with it
Like my daughter
She likes the music but only mine, but my son absolutely hates it doesn't want everything to do with it
He was young mom
I really like the words, but I don't like the AI part. I'm okay
You know that's that's valid because we've grown up with music our whole entire life. My dad played his whole
brothers play all of it
But it's like you know, well, you all have like, you know, you're like, yeah, I would love to like, you know
you know record every song in a studio and have like backing music, it's thousands and thousands of dollars to actually produce live music.
Right.
I have to like, you know, maybe it's like, maybe, but it's like, you know...
There's certain people of certain ages like they're not allowed to probably use it in school and things like that
Or there's probably like a whole different like you know wave approaching it for you for like the younger people nowadays
They're probably you know because I'm sure it's just like very attempting to like hey
Just like you know instead of writing a paper to ten minutes just put it in the thing
You know it's like so but I think so I think that they're gonna have to make some concessions for
the writing with like using it for writing because
It's like everyone's going to be doing it, and it's even the parents are going to put it to, I don't know, it's like, but then it will be, it'll be a whole process of like, you know, learning.
like adapting. Sure, but I don't I don't see it actually getting rid of regular music though.
I mean like band music. There always be musicians and regular music and it's like you know I mean
there'll always be like it's like artists too and then it's like and then you know it's gonna be
maybe more valuable that they'll be able to charge more and stuff for original works and stuff like
that. Yeah but they're everybody's acting like AI is going to push real music out and I'm like how.
Yeah, how for people that are like making it like that learn how to like DJ beats and stuff like that
And then it's like you know kind of like the yeah
I just gonna do it like much even like better faster like you like it's not so certain certain like aspects people that are already
Like chronic musicians, maybe like it will be like yeah, but it's like people that play instruments
It's like they're always gonna be in demand for like live
I don't know it's like there's really no reason though. So it's like, you know, it will replace a lot of jobs
I mean, but it's a bit that's technology anyway
Yeah, that was like the whole problem. I was this industrial
Industrial revolution was up you know, putting things in factories and making everything streamlined and having machines make everything and people were like
Kind of stuff that like, oh my gosh, you know, but it was like what do you want to have people like doing these jobs that like the mission can do
It's like a calculator and like learning like stuff like, you know
With the calculator, yeah, so you don't really have to like learn add and subtract that much better. You should learn how to add and subtract basic math, but it's like
They're huge
It's just kind of easier to like use a calculator sometimes, right? And it's like is that like
Such a big cheat like I don't I don't think so
Well, if kids go through school now and not have to go through your band, I will throw a fit
That's that's it. That's all I'm gonna say
Yeah
Because like my daughter plays let's say trumpet
sax and
the
trumpet sax and
clarinet, there we go. I can't think of the word.
Yeah, but you've got autotune, which is already a cheat if you want to go ahead and
call it that, then you've got all the people in the studio making it completely different. There's very few
where you go live, I mean like bands that go live.
At concerts and sound the same that as they do in the studio because you've got all the people mixing it in
Whatever that there's very few artists that I've ever heard that sounded
amazing even without music
Yeah, and that I don't appreciate with the the autotune. I think that's cheating far more
I can't even sing, you know, the people I can't even sing like in real life.
Yeah, exactly. We'll never get rid of actual musicians, never.
I mean, I will go ahead and say that I'm biased because there was a lot of good music and since
my dad's a musician, there was tons of music always. You know, all these bands that nobody's
ever heard of that I got to hear him because my dad played them.
So, yeah, I I don't think it'll ever
That's another thing is like the talented people is not necessarily the talented people that are gonna be though
It's gonna be like, you know, whoever gets signed for certain reasons, right? It is like right and so there's like a lot of
Nepotism in the industry. There's a lot of like
Mickey Mouse club. Yeah
Stuff and so like going to a club or going to I mean granted. I don't go to clubs and never have but you know all these places where
small dive bars where somebody's singing and they sound amazing, there's people in
there that go oh my god we need to sign her or him you know because of their
voice and that's not going to change people are still gonna have that talent
oh thank fuck yes Darryl I really hope so I hate auto-tune because that's
exactly what you were saying psyche you know even if you don't have talent use
It's like I'm tempted to like there's a there's a thing where I can like on the
Program I use music there's a thing where you can like put a sample of your voice in there and then have the songs play
You know with your voice and stuff
And it's like that'd be great, but I like having a female voice, like a lot of the time I just like
personally like listen for like female voices usually and like kind of like male voices singing
kind of epic songs are kind of like cheesy. I don't know. I like country, I like males that
sing country music and like like the sort of rock songs, but I love female musicians. I love like
the female singers and but but then again it's like not like it's too popular. I like, you know,
like Adele. I have a really hard time with the new stuff, yeah.
It's really funny though, if somebody says,
what's your favorite song, how can you answer that?
Because it depends on the minute, for me,
what kind of a mood am I in?
If I'm in a country mood, here's the country song
I'm listening to right now.
If it's metal, here's the metal song I really like.
It just depends.
There'll be classical thrown in there sometimes.
Right, I mean, I like all kinds of music really like and I when I listen to really my personal life is like, you know
basically like
Hindu chanting and Sanskrit and like that like it really it's like I love Indian music and stuff
But I do have like I mean Indian but it's like, you know, I don't think but I get really into it where I get like
You know into like the chanting and like the like everything's in Sanskrit and like learning to do like the really difficult chance and like, you know
And it's like really fulfilling and agree, but it's like I don't people are gonna be like that sounds weird
that sounds like
They're not gonna understand so I just kind of like
They were like a little bit share a little bit less of that stuff, but
I think people shouldn't really look into whatever they're interested in.
I just don't want to like push an agenda really on people,
especially because this is already a cult and people are thinking that's like going to be like serious cult.
And it's a half a half of it's like a satire or something like that.
You know, it's like, but it's like, you know, people can take it as serious or
non-serious as they want to, but it's not how I'm trying to like.
Be worshiped. It's not me trying to
To get people to follow me or anything. I say I would if I do create anything I would like to create a lot of leaders
I'd like to create a lot of people that are
Streaming and stuff like that and I would enjoy enjoying it and like, you know, I hope to inspire people and stuff like that
But I don't want to like
Tell people what to do or anything like that. I've been very in for personal freedom for everybody. I'm libertarian
So I'm very living that live and like, you know
You know legalize most things, you know, because
You know, there's a lot of victimless crimes. There's a lot of
Like, you know, the whole drug war there's been like even like people like, you know
like basically
Most people like I know that there's a lot of effects for other people like when somebody's like addicted to drugs
But most of the time it's just hurting them the most, you know, and it's like, um, I don't know
I'm glad there's there's a, you know, weed at least is allowed in California. It's like because
When you something take the edge off out here, California is a hard place to to live, you know, it's like very
It's beautiful. Okay, but it's very
Everyone's like looking to be somebody or like that or like to know somebody or something like that
And then there's like a lot of people from all over the country come here
To like make it and it's like a lot of them don't and so there's like the big like homeless population and
Or like or like, you know, like a lot of people that haven't been able to make it here because it's so expensive too
I've never been to California so I don't know but I can imagine. Yeah, I've lived here all my life. Yeah, it's just a crazy place to live
I mean, it's nice. I wouldn't live here if my family wasn't like, you know
Wanting me to be here
Because it's like probably
You know, but I get plays much less expensive in like the south or I would even go to other countries, you know
I wouldn't mind like
I'd be afraid of like in the I think my dad was always afraid of be pushing a shopping cart around here
So something like that. I would not go to India at all
Because evidently, a woman in India is a bad thing anyway.
Well, I would say it's maybe more dangerous for women.
And I wouldn't go without it.
Madan Blavatsky used to go to all these places alone.
When women weren't really allowed to travel,
I don't know if you know who she is.
She's a Russian.
I don't.
She's a Russian mystic.
She founded the Theosopical Society.
I don't know if El Frank Baum was a theosophist.
It's like Theo means God.
And like Sophie means like, you know, like a, like a.
like, knowledge, like, so, like, you know, philosophy. So, um...
Yeah, so she her name is Madame Blabatsky. She wrote all these books
But she was like this kind of like, you know stocky woman and she would like go on a train in India and like throw plant flowers across
I think the flowers are so that it's a plant and it's up, but she was like, you know, she was very
Influential and like the spiritual community. She was up. She was also high-ranking mason, too
When the only women that was even allowed to to be in it. Yeah, I thought that was the only guy only thing
Vader, my video is better. Don't worry. It's fine.
The video is better. Vader is telling me that his video is better. It's not.
Byron. Byron, I don't think yours is better.
Yeah, Byron is down in the side chat. That's Vader.
Let me play one more song. Let me see. 5, 6, 7, okay, hold on.
Wait, did we just see that one?
That's her legend.
A myth?
Maybe a legend.
Okay, okay.
I'll have to go on to my channel.
See you.
Bye.
What happens when I'm just bad at this one?
Watch this one.
I was just in no surrender when I heard it was horn.
Hi, Peter.
No, it's not.
OK, here we go.
Not caged eternity.
Through the alleys of neon sin
Where truth wears lace and shadows grin
Psych walks a flicker in the
smoke
Each breath a spell, the darkness spoke
Serpents whisper love like prayer
Honey lies perfume the air
But the panther waits where the moonlight fell
Guardian boasts in the web of
There's a bell
Chains of charm
Velvet deceit
Every trap
For him to defeat
But faith is a weapon
Full of forged inflame
He's bled through the labyrinth kiss the abyss
Shackens with angels who lie like this every fall was a prophecy told
Every scar a sigil
that one too. Except, except song fantastic song fantastic. But
the video, I hate the spiders and plus that chick has bigger
titties than me. But yeah, spiders.
But the spiders actually protect their young or they carry their young or something like that. Oh, they carry. Yes, they do
Remember I said that I lived on a farm
Lay out in the country. Yeah, there's these big wolf spiders. I think it's wolf spider
I was in the dark on the computer
This one went by I
Smushed it because I can't stand them. They scare me and a bunch of her babies took off and I was oh god
I lost my mind. Oh my gosh
This lady
That's Susan powder, I have no idea she got some wild hair though
I just thought it's very tan lady on well, there's some hot guys on tiktok
I don't know a little bit a little bit of a tiktok scent. I don't know
Give me some people. I don't have anything. I have tiktok
You know, do you have it?
I don't have it no it's good Instagram because I got monetized on tiktok within like
Three days or something like that you just need like how the hell do you get monetized on tiktok because um you can well
If you you have a fan club you can have a fan club in the see I don't really make money from tiktok though
I have none on enough but um
Yeah, you can have a bank that we all can also be in the tick tock shop and like sell your own stuff
You can like have you can have a store that I just recently heard about the tick tock shop
I had no clue about that one at all
And there's a lot of people that are just like selling their stuff on there
I know because you can just do that, but um
And then there's just people like just sitting there and like just like flirting with people or playing games and stuff
But you know like some people are making good money on it
And I like if you think actually like doing tarot on it
It's like I get like thousands of likes like in one episode because it's like people can like you can like something as much as you
Want it's not just like one life like I but I finally
I have likes or something in this chat tonight.
It's like, on TikTok, I have like thousands, right?
And then it's like people like,
I can do like the really quick, like one card reads,
like, and just do the readings and stuff.
Like if you put it on the screen, like ask your question.
People just come in real quick,
usually the last question and go, like it is like,
and then, you know, if they want to like,
book a reading or something like that,
there's ways to advertise for that too, but.
That it sounds like good advertisement. Yeah. Yeah, I mean
I'm really into marketing and it's like just figuring out ways to monetize and I've tried a lot of stuff
I've always been able to make a decent
You're a Capricorn. I am not surprised in the slightest. Exactly. Yeah, Capricorns are very about like business
And money makers. Yep. Saturn, you know Saturn
I was also born with like Saturn and Libra or so Saturn and Jupiter like on top of each other basically
They're the same degree on the like that when I was born
So it's in the sign of Libra. And so it's basically they're like this
You know, they're basically evenly matched in Libra, which is like the scales, right? Then there's Pluto
in the thing, I have Pluto and Libra too, which is like Pluto's kind of like the death thing.
But I'm very much just as Saturn is actually exalted in Libra,
and then I have all the Capricorn placements, and so I have a kind of like very lucky,
a very, very well-aspected chart, I would say. I have a pretty interesting chart if you're,
Yeah, like, you know, if you find out you're like, you know, because all the planets are like these archetypes, like Mercury, you know, and Jupiter's planet, like a very good beneficial planet always considered a very beneficent, and then Saturn's considered a very
Wait, so both or neither
What's that the father the father of the mean teacher do you mean both or neither?
Well, I think that like Saturn is more like the father, but it's like but I was just thinking that it's like
It's like kind of like a mean dad.
It's like kind of like the dad that's like, you know,
you never, you never, you know,
they mean for the expectations or whatever.
So it wasn't like, I know it was like
a lot more like Jupiter type, like, which is like,
he was just like very like into like drinking wine
and like, you know, like love, have, have enjoy life,
have fun, you know, like we don't live forever.
And it's like, you just really love life and stuff.
But,
He didn't like to think about death or like that and I was very like comfortable with the thought of it and stuff like that just because you know
Saturn's about it basically the material world. It's it's like the Capricorn's the devil, you know, it's like a we
We we rule the material world. We were given this world, but you know, it's like
It's not an easy world to live in like either and it's like we rule it
But we do rule it where the cardinal earth sign
Yeah, I'm just burdened man
Oh, you're your bird man with it's horses. No for the man for the man the bull
Yeah, for the end the bull
You know it's like but for the end the bull is like he just had these really beautiful eyes and eyelashes and like
He'd love to fall in love and love love and stuff like that. I mean, I love love too. It's just like mine is like it's like I
Know it's being gay is a weird thing because it's like, you know, first of all, there's like no
I mean it's kind of so easy to have sex or to hook up with people that it's not very appealing to me and it's like just like
People that sleep with a lot of people. It was just I grew up in the 80s where you just hear people dying of AIDS and stuff
And so it was like I was always kind of very diseased
And I was like well then when I had sex it was not even that great to like
Risk it unless you're like it I said I have to be in love with the person and so I really haven't been
Oh, but I did my longest relationship with a woman
2012 I did her for three months. She was like this Heyoka type
Really interesting lady, but um taught me a lot of stuff that revealed to me like
Like some of the true magic in the world and they taught me I'm very interested in like spirituality and things
But the last very long it was kind of bad, but it was still interesting. I felt like I just had a this
drive to have sex with a woman because I was like that was like like
I had to be balanced or something like that. I just couldn't like as I couldn't like live my life and not have like
Done that or something like I felt like it was part of like the initiation of the world to at least have sex once
And so I did have sex exactly
And hated every second
Yeah, I was like, you know, we had
We actually these kind of like things on youtube are they kind of like these stupid like
erotic videos on YouTube where it's like, they're so dumb.
But it's like, she was like, she was in her fifties
and stuff like that.
I don't know.
It's like-
Oh, there you go.
She wanted to create a nest and she basically made
big bird's nest inside my house and like, you know.
You know, this spaghetti dinner one night, I'm sure
it had like, you know, something in the spaghetti sauce,
you know, because, you know, she was a witch, but,
but, you know, I don't know if you get that reference,
but yeah.
There was like something people put in spaghetti sauce sometimes and I think she did
I don't know if you know what I'm talking about but
No, but it makes it a lot easier. Well, it's red, right?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, that's just a hint. I don't know. I don't yeah the what I'm thinking in my head
I really don't want to say out loud wishcraft is it's wishcraft. It's like, you know, uh-huh. Uh-huh
So I don't but yeah, you know
But uh, only this spaghetti sauce, but you can drink the, I'm not, not drink the Kool-Aid, but like,
it depends on, I don't know who's making the Kool-Aid, you know.
Hey Paige, I haven't seen Paige forever. Hey, how are you doing sweetie?
Oh my god. Hello Paige.
Do I put a fairy page song when she comes in? I think I should, let me see, I need to go.
Listen, KZ, I had nothing to do with that fucking conversation.
Oh yeah, that was, okay, let me hold on.
I'm going to get the page video to see. I can sing the song.
Hairful of that, that's very pretty. I'm sorry, that's not very good.
That was my attempt. Okay, let me find the song actually. Go to my...
She's Breezy Bee. Hey, Breezy's here? Oh my god.
No, our page said that she's been a busy bee.
She's a busy bee. Yep, she has been because I haven't seen you around the
music video. I recently changed my computer over so I need to like download these songs.
Is this a song playing? Oh my god, it's a song playing. Okay.
Why are you going to be able to find this? I have like a thousand videos now.
Yeah, I don't know if I'll find it but I'll look I'll look real quick. I think I don't know what it looks like
I have a lot of the same imagery that I use. I see a lot of storm clouds. I see a lot of like
Beach
Well for me page hell, yeah
Okay, I gotta go see that
I need to see you what my earrings look like.
I hate that you don't get notified
as somebody's community pose.
Oh, like you can really pose like when they,
but you don't get to know.
Yeah, um, I don't know about, I don't,
yeah, I think there's a way to put it in that,
like to get notified when someone's posing or something.
Oh, is there?
I think so.
Oh, those got some.
Yeah, it's like, I get,
Notice this for everything. I got I was getting too many so I had to turn I think turn off a few settings, but
Okay, okay, is this a hole is this that let me check. It's gonna be the summer song though
Found it. I found it. That was my first try. Wow. It's so good. Okay
Okay, wow
I sent this to you page, by the way, it's on your, it's on your, uh, this quote, uh, uh, okay, yeah, I don't know, I have to, I have to, I have to post it somewhere, I think, on, uh, on YouTube, but it's too stealthy, I haven't yet, here we go.
She lines up a shot, swing, smooth, no range
That's my Canadian darling
That's Prairie Pace
Cards on the table, incense in the air
She reads like a prayer, sweet voice humming, heart full of sage
Every word she speaks feels like a golden page
Oh prairie page, wild and free, cool as a breeze through the evergreens
Alexander's heart's gone on
She takes her laughter flies
Northern lights dancing in her eyes
She don't fake, she don't play games
She's the calm in the storm
The spark in the flame
Yeah, she's a-
We eat in the other sense, but it's that boot.
So it's Canadian, it's like, that's, it's, it's, it's.
I love that, yeah.
That foggy tree thing, oh my God, I love that.
Foggy trees.
Nature's my thing, I swear.
It always makes me do a reset.
It's amazing, I love it.
Well, I'm very lucky to like live by the ocean
because it is kind of like, at least I have a big,
like there's not like a lot of forest around or anything,
so which I love, but.
How dare you?
I would love beaches.
I love beaches, yeah, the beach.
No.
You don't like it?
You don't like beaches?
Listen, I used to want to be an oceanographer when I got this great, big book I found in
the art cell when I was probably six, seven, something like that.
And they have beautiful pictures of all this stuff.
until I got to the page of the stuff that wants to kill you.
And then I immediately said,
nope, don't want to be an oceanographer,
I'm gonna be a vet and said.
Ha ha ha ha.
You know, once you see JAWS too,
it's like, you're never gonna want to go swimming
in the ocean again.
I mean, it's like.
Mm-mm, no thank you.
It's like, there's two, it's two like, you know.
It's just too big and then you can't see there's something you can't see and you can't see yes, exactly
Especially when you go deeper and deeper and oh my god. Nope. No, thank you
Scuba divers are pretty
There's a guy from naked and afraid he lives around here, but he lives in his car
He's around here and then um we have um the guy from swiss's sister de snyder. I've seen him at the starbucks
Oh my god. I love de snyder film be a watcher too. And so they filmed it here, but um we don't go
So it's interesting you might
You might go live today. Maybe okay. That's fine. Vader
Don't be mean to anybody
Well, he has a show is Byron. Do you if you want to give me tell me your channel or tell them on your channels own posts that I
I do want to share one's channel and like be a place
I'm still doing my panel version my psyche verse, whatever. It's just like it takes it's like right now. It's like
There's so much stuff on the way trying to like, you know, keep it like but I will put it up eventually and like help advertise people like
You know a lot more than I am like, but yeah, I can like list people on it will show say when they're live
In order to do that, you know, I have to, like, have, um, there's, like, a little, you know, there's, like, probably, like, it's easy to get, like, there's, like, a little text key you need to give and everything, and that's the only way I will tell when you're, like, exactly live, but I can actually, like, put them on, uh, and show it.
And then come to find out on some of these that I wanted to get any notifications on at all. It'd unsubscribe me
So did you like give the bell checked like the bell?
Okay, yeah
So it's weird. Yeah, that will happen. Sometimes people will be unsubscribed from channels for like no reason and stuff like that
I don't know why it happens like it does happen like
Occasionally I don't appreciate that shit at all. Yeah, cuz I rely on those
You know, I'm not gonna go to somebody's channel, especially if it's somebody that I haven't seen in a while. Yeah, that I would like to see
But you know, I have the attention span of a nap. So
That's why I got the website is because now on my website. I have my show
I showed
There it's like you can it's always playing on my channel is like posted there
So when I go live it will say I'm live and stuff and then you can watch it on the show
There's the chats there and everything
Wait, you have a channel too
It's like I think it's like still I can just work on it like a little bit of day, but um, I think
I mean because it's like a
The way it works is like, you know, I spend credits like to like build it and stuff.
Oh, okay, the site see the site exactly
Page is absolutely right. We aren't supposed to be down there is her conclusion. I wholeheartedly agree
No ocean. Thank you
You do not have to be mean Vader
You don't
Okay, so here I'll show you. So yeah, this is my website. This is cultofstikey.com
It's actually gonna be really amazing because there's a lot of space in my dream website
It's one of my
Okay, so you go to it. I see
So do you see it? Hold on. Can you see are you on the screen? No, it's not on the screen. I do. Yeah
Yeah, that's great. A sanctuary a sanctuary for the exiled. Yeah. Yeah
so
Oh, and it's C-cult, not K-cult.
So, let me see, do they fix this thing?
They fix it, okay, no.
I can't see the rest of it.
I was guessing on exile in a storm borne.
Okay, there we go.
Exile the absurd in a storm borne, okay.
And then, so this thing, okay, I have this.
Bunch of things like so I have the video playing somewhere in there. I have the troll decoder
You can go the troll decoder. I didn't get really troll today
But if they you know someone types you suck or something like that, and then I go troll decoder, right?
It goes
And decodes it and I'll say
This is the raw expression of generalized frustration the decoded truth
I am currently feeling profound dissatisfaction possibly with my own life or recent efforts and I'm projecting that feeling of sucking on to you
And so there you go. There's a like it. Yeah, so there's a little troll decoder and there's a troll. There's a free
The troll decoder book. You don't see the page. I'm sorry. It's right on the screen
No, he doesn't see page
I guess she has you blocked that if you don't see her in the chat because she's talking
Maybe she might be on the other channel though. No, no, that's why she's on the KULT of psyche not CULT of psyche
Okay, what else I have on the site. I have like a lot of cool stuff. Oh, I love the cursor
Oh yeah, the cursor makes like little stuff, I have music, I do have music and stuff playing too, but it's not there.
Oh yeah, so I'm going to show you the live stream. So if you click on live stream, I don't know why the banner's not up, it should have a banner up, okay?
To fix that. Because sometimes I need to reduce stuff over and over again.
So it has a theater, oh, oh, oh, they take down the whole theater.
Yeah, okay, yeah, I see what happened.
I had it playing live, but then...
They've replaced it with this video. I already had okay. I see what they did
Okay, but it will I'll get working again. It's like it's just fucking
Looks really really cool. Thank you. Thank you
I've been working really hard on it like from a few months now
I just want to get a perfect and it's gonna have a really cool stuff there
Don't have it. I just have my other channel going on. Yeah, because I'm just getting people like I'm so people are still figuring out this
Because if you can come to this channel though
It's like the CULT of psyche because the other one's my backup channel
I'm really trying to get people back to this one because I don't usually broadcast on the other one right now
Okay. Oh, that's the one that I am on. I might be in the KULT
Because I am you know, it's like because when you're golf off YouTube for a few weeks they
You know, it doesn't like
There's no there's no track because I got probably I got basically got my channel brought back at a miracle
Like they're basically there was a like somebody else intervened. Okay, like that. I didn't know was even a
Like a possibility that that the certain party intervened
And I won't say on your behalf. Yeah. Yeah, and when they were able to because they're either either like a partner
Or they work for YouTube or like they
very high like something it has to be something like that because uh I was I was it was I was done
I was like I don't know it's just like I had been
My two appeals were refused and I wasn't on another appeal.
And so, and then it's like two days before like,
the, yeah, it's just crazy how, how,
but I was gone for three weeks basically.
And so that's like three weeks of like,
since I was gone for so long,
it's like basically like I hadn't posted for three weeks
or done anything.
And like also like,
nobody had visited my page for three weeks
because there was not even there, right?
And so it's like, so the algorithm got weighed.
Knocked off for me and the other night. I was on there was like no people. I was like, oh
But uh, okay, so I hang on just a minute. Yeah, so the
AI songs that you've been uploading, are those on the K1 or the C1?
They're on both. I've been putting them on as I do them, like as I premiere them and stuff.
Okay, alright.
They're on both. There's a bunch on the other one, yeah, because I was like three weeks,
I did a lot of music that three weeks, but I'm doing a lot now too.
Well, like I said, I get notifications for some of them.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, because it's like, I think you get three notifications a day.
And so
I don't have the influence for what?
What are you saying?
There was always like an annoying. Yeah, I understand. I love the influence. Okay. I don't care. I don't I don't know what's happening
But I do have to take my puppy out. I appreciate it so much for you playing my music and
Let me out. Hey, thank you so much. It's great. It's fun hanging out. Thank you
You're very welcome. Can I page? Okay. Good night guys. Bye. Be nice. So let me just tell you Darryl
Because you're saying I don't have the influence for that to happen for a test someone intervene
Okay, Darryl, do you see I'm here
See have you heard of anybody getting their third their channel back after it's been taken down for like over like three weeks, right?
Have you ever heard of that?
No
After being denied the twice and something no, okay, so
I'll play the song I was going to play the whole time, and then I'll probably like go soon, but here it's funny out with you guys. Love you
Before the stars
I am the whisper in the dark you fear
And the truth you wake to let begin
I am the mirror, no lies survives
Come close below
Step in
Your scars unbraid them into truth anew
The night goes down before me
The galaxy's kneeling gold
For the fire in my heart beat
Is older than the...
The shock that breaks the whole
Crystal Marie on a midnight stream
Neon eyes and conspiracy dreams
Talking cults in the desert sands
Tattoo maps and shaking hands
She's got screenshots, names and dates
A ten-four halo, ceiling fades in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's hot, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbols sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crazy clothes, games and traffickers
Little saboteurs, truth or fiction doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and socketed
She's part over cold, part in a net myth Half the room's scared, the rest's obsessed
Her eyeliner is sharp as a truth, dissected And every theory leaves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in Because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin